[Music]
so
how do you do i'm the king
i'm the king of gondo land
how do you do i'm the queen
hello
i'm princess sylvia
[Music]
oh sylvia sylvia
hello i'm bob i'm the gardener
how do you do i'm corvix
thank you kovacs
hi i'm mazzy
big muzzy
[Music]
good morning good morning
good morning i'm norman
good morning
[Music]
good
afternoon
[Music]
good afternoon
good evening
[Music]
good night good night good night good
night
i'm strong
i'm fat i'm fat
i'm beautiful
i'm clever
i'm brave
[Music]
strong fat beautiful
clever and brave
[Music]
you're strong yes i am
and you're fat yes i am
and she's beautiful yes
she is he's brave
and he's clever no no i'm
clever i am clever clever
clever strong fat
beautiful clever and brave
[Music]
i'm big big muzzy
big small
i'm big muzzy
and i'm big muzzy
[Music]
i've got a bag a big bag i've got a map
i've got a hamburger
i've got a bike a motorbike
i've got a computer
i've got a garden look
i've got plums
i've got peaches
[Music]
i've got grapes
i like plums
[Music]
i like peaches
i like grapes
and i like grapes
[Music]
hello mommy hello daddy
can i have a peach please
[Music]
i like hamburgers
[Applause]
[Music]
can i have a hamburger please
here you are thank you
can i have a salad please
here you are
you can i have a drink
please here you are
thank you can i have an ice cream
[Music]
thank you can i have a wash
please
[Music]
can i have a peach please daddy
yes a peach
a peach thank you
can i have a plum and some grapes please
yes a plum and some grapes
a plum and some grapes
thank you
[Music]
meow a plum
a peach a grape
a plum a peach
some grapes
a plum a plum
a plum three plums
jackpot
[Applause]
plums plums plums
[Music]
bob yes
trees trees
yes how many trees
count one
two three four
five six seven
eight nine ten
[Music]
how many trees are there
one two
three
five six
seven eight
[Music]
how many bushes are there
there are two four six
eight ten and how many
flowers are there
flowers yes yes
how many flowers a hundred
two hundred three hundred i don't know
[Music]
i don't know
a hundred and seven a hundred
and eight a hundred and nine
a hundred and ten
bob
can i have a rose please
thank you i like roses
and i like you oh
look i've got a rose
i've got a plum and a peach and some
grapes
a hamburger and a map
and i've got
a bike i love you
and i love you
off we go no
no no i love the princess
i love sylvia
[Music]
you love me
off we go
[Music]
i love you
[Applause]
the gardener loves the princess
yes yes no no
no the princess loves the gardener
yes yes no
no come on
off we go follow me
bye
[Music]
[Applause]
hi hello
[Music]
daddy mommy korvax
[Applause]
[Music]
oh mommy
i love princess sylvia take him away
take him away take him away take him
away
take him away take him away
take him away take him away take him
away
take him away
thank you
take him away number 19
number 19
number 19.
9 10 11
12 13 14
15 16 17
18 19 20
oh 19.
a monster hello
i'm mozzie big
[Music]
the big muzzy story
[Applause]
[Music]
i'm hungry
i'm hungry i'm
hungry
i'm hungry
lovely
[Music]
like clocks
hmm
[Music]
i'm hungry
plums plums lovely plums
what's this it's a plum
[Music]
oh
what what's this
i don't know it's a bike what's this
i don't know it's a spaceship
what's this it's a clock
what's this it's a clock no
it's a parking meter what's this
it's a typewriter no it's a computer
what's this it's a cat
what's that what's that it's my bell
it's my belly
what's this it's a plan
eat it
[Music]
yuck i don't
like it look how about
this what is it it's a peach
eat it it's lovely
eat it
no horrible i
don't like it it's horrible
i don't like this and i
don't like that
this that
that this
[Music]
i don't like this and i
don't like that
i don't like these and i don't
like those i don't like
these and i don't like
those
ah what's that
what's that thing what thing
that thing that
thing it's a parking meter
a parking meter
yes you
[Music]
i like this
i like parking meters
[Music]
hello monster i'm muzzy
hello i'm a friend
who are you what's your name
pepe what's your name
bob who are you
[Music]
who
who are you i'm the king
no it isn't for you
who are you i'm the queen
[Music]
who's this it's the princess
no it isn't for her who's that
it's corvax you're corvex
yes i am
this is for you here you are
thank you
who are you i'm norman
bye no who are you
[Music]
i'm bob i'm a gardener
who are you where do you come from
there up there
where there
up there i come from
up there there
[Music]
where
where do you come from france
where do you come from britain
where do you come from germany
where do you come from italy
where do you come from greece
and i come from japan bye
i come from up there
and now i'm down here
i'm here too oh
sylvia s
y l v
i a i
love you b o
b
a a b
b c
[Music]
h i
i j j
k k l
l m m
n n o
o p p
q q r
r s s
t t u
u v v
w w x
x y y z
z
sylvia stop it korvax
go away i love bob
i love you sylvia oh go away
stop sylvia stop
come here oh
sylvia stop come here
korvax go away
stop come here
look
listen go away
[Music]
stop come here
look listen
go away
sylvia sylvia
[Music]
ah sylvia
i love you
s y l v
i a
that's right kovacs
labs
the body
a head
an eye an eye
a nose a mouth
a an ear
a neck
an arm an arm
hand a hand
a leg a leg
a foot a foot
good good
my sylvia i've got you now
lovely yeah that's good
where is it
here it is and this
and this
[Music]
now go
oh
sylvia my sylvia
now i've got you
m u double
dead y
v o b
you and me
we we're friends
[Music]
we are baldwin mom are we
me and you we are two two great friends
are we
hey look what look up there
bars bars lovely delicious
yummy bars oh no no thanks
yes eat the bars
one two three
four five we're free
you're free and i'm free
we are free
you are free and i am free
we are free you and me we are free
free yes we're free off we go
[Music]
i'm free
i'm wet i'm cold
and i'm hungry but
i'm free
[Music]
hot
hungry
thirsty
wet
dry
i'm thirsty have a drink
it's hot oh sorry
i'm hungry have a hamburger
i'm hot have a shower
i'm wet
have a towel
i'm cold have a sweater
i'm tired have a rest
bob where are you
bob mazzy
here where i can't
see you i'm here in the tree
what a tree this tree
where are you now i'm
[Music]
where
where are you under the box
where are you on the box
where are you in the box
where are you in front of the box
where are you behind the box
where are you between the boxes
where's the box over there
where's the box now over here
in on under
in front of behind
between
are you all right are you all right
oh yes just cold
and wet and hungry
where's the palace it's over there
[Music]
there it is over there
that's the palace
sylvia's there
listen can you
hear me
[Music]
look can you see me
can you talk yes i can
can you walk no i can't
let me try again
now can you walk
yes i can can you
run no
i can't let me try again
sylvia do you
love me no i don't i don't like you
oh sylvia now i can run
bye sylvia stop
come back
[Music]
what's happening
i can walk i can talk
i can hear i can see
who are you am i you are you me
[Music]
i can jump i can swim i can run
this is fun i am you you are me
who
[Music]
who are you i'm sylvia i'm sylvia
i'm sylvia i'm sylvia i'm sylvia
i'm sylvia
you're sylvia yes we
are six sylvias
yes who would they
sylvia
six sylvias
you've got a green dress you've got a
red
dress she's got a blue dress i
like brown
i've got a yellow dress yellow is for
happiness
black and white look all right
but i like
[Music]
black and white
yellow blue
red green
brown
see ya
[Music]
do
head and shoulders knees and toes
knees and toes eyes and mouth and
ears and nose ears and nose
eyes and
[Music]
where are we we're in the garden
what your garden
no silly the palace gardens
look there's sylvia
what's she doing she's doing her
exercises
knees and nose knees and toes
quick behind this thing what thing
the statue are you all right
no we aren't we're hungry
can we have some food please can i have
a
clock please a clock
excuse me yes
a clock he likes clocks
somebody's coming
who is it i don't know
i can't see shh
okay oh no
it's raining look
wait over there okay
see you this evening when
seven o'clock see you at seven this
evening
seven o'clock right
what's the time now
it's eight o'clock
hello
no i'm busy i'm having breakfast
it's one o'clock
hello
no i'm busy i'm having
lunch
it's seven o'clock
[Music]
hello no
i'm busy i'm having dinner
it's nine o'clock
hello
no i'm busy i'm having a bar
it's ten o'clock
hello
busy no i'm going to bed
good night
[Music]
one o'clock it's lunch time
it's lunch time dear i'm coming
it's lunch time sylvia
i'm not very well can i have lunch in my
room what's the matter
i've got a terrible headache
[Music]
a headache stomachache
toothache
come in what's the matter i've got a
headache doctor
a headache take this thank you
doctor next
what's the matter
[Music]
stomach ache take this thank you doctor
nix what's the matter
i've got toothache doctor toothache
take this thank you doctor
next what's the matter
i've got backache doctor backache
take this thank you doctor
a headache
stay in your room dear and have a rest
lunch for the princess in her room
sylvia isn't very well she's
got a headache
she's got a headache she's having lunch
in her room
his her
her knife his knife
his fork her fork
her glass his glass
his plate her plate
a bowl his bowl
his crown her crown
a headache phew
[Music]
hello silvia how are you now
how am i i'm fine
thank you where are you going
i'm going to the swimming pool see you
have a nice swim dear
hello sylvia how are you now
feeling better feeling better
i'm fine good good good
where are you going i'm going to the
tennis court
see you have a nice game dear
sylvia's feeling better now she's
playing
tennis playing tennis
no she isn't she's having a swim
hello mommy hello
daddy bye
[Music]
is it still working
yes it's working
good how many sylvias
are there six no
there are seven
is it still raining no it's fine now
it's getting dark
what's the time it's nearly seven
o'clock
it gets dark at seven in autumn
it gets dark at seven autumn
[Music]
autumn
winter
spring
[Music]
summer
in autumn it gets dark at seven
in winter it gets dark at five
in spring it gets dark at seven
in summer it gets dark at nine
september october november
december january
february march
april may june
july august
january february march
april may june july
august september
monday tuesday
wednesday thursday
friday saturday
sunday on monday i play football
[Music]
on tuesday i play basketball
on wednesday i go roller skating
on thursday i do my exercises
on friday i go swimming
[Music]
on saturday i play golf
and on sunday we play tennis
[Music]
when
when do you play football on monday
when do you play basketball on tuesday
when do you go roller skating on
wednesday
when do you do your exercises on
thursday
when do you go swimming on friday
when do you play golf on saturday
when do you play tennis on sunday
and it's sunday today and we're playing
tennis now
where is princess sylvia's room
there where on the first floor
no it's on the second floor oh
there are three rooms on the second
floor
which one is it is it the one on the
left
no it isn't is it the one on the right
no it isn't is it the one in the middle
yes it is it's the one in the middle
it's the one in the middle
what about the room up there the one
on the top floor that's corvax's room
it's the computer room
[Music]
you
food clocks
7 p.m i've got some food
i've got some clocks and it's nearly
7 o'clock okay
open the door quietly
look round carefully
run downstairs quickly
hello sylvia hello
that's me
oh it's seven and bob's waiting
ah that's me again
[Music]
seven o'clock it's
dinner time sylvia yes mommy
yes mommy yes mommy yes
mommy yes mummy yes mommy
yes mummy
many are there
there are three in the kitchen four in
the
home there's one by the fireplace there
are two against the wall
there's one in the sitting room bouncing
on the chairs
and four are having lots of fun sliding
down the stairs
there are hundreds in the garden picking
all the flowers and
[Music]
appearing everywhere
room upstairs what's he doing
go and see quick
[Music]
listen wow it's sylvia
oh bob i'm frightened
why why are you frightened
because there are lots of sylvias in the
palace
sylvie excuse me
have you got any clocks oh
muzzy here you are
muzzy why do you eat clocks because i
like them of course
[Music]
why
oh dear he's crying
why are you crying because i can't reach
the
apple why can't you reach the apple
because i'm small i can reach the apple
yes why because you're
tall right here you are
thanks bye
hey that's my apple and my
bike come back
come back that's mine
gotcha now
is this my bike yes
it's yours yes it's mine
and where's my apple you can't have it
why not because it's in here
ah i
see corvax
the computer are you going
to the computer room come on follow me
[Music]
stop the computer i can't
your majesty of course you can
it's your computer yes i know
it's mine but i can't stop it
well i can stop it excuse me
excuse me
don't do that
[Music]
look there's one and there's one
and there oh there are lots of them
there's a fat one oh that one's
better look there's a big one
that's a bigger one over there come on
mazzy
[Music]
i'm big i'm
bigger the first ones big
the second ones bigger i'm
small yes the third one's
small and the fourth one's
smaller the fifth
is tall the sixth is
taller the seventh is uh
fat and the eighth
is fatter
[Laughter]
fatter
help me corvex i can't your majesty
oh no it's silly you're silly
oh dear what can i do
ah i can run away
the helicopter help
help corvex corvex
excuse me your majesty what's happening
where are you going to the helicopter
help oh
the king's in the computer kovacs
stop come back
corvette hey
stop
[Music]
mazzy go up there to the computer room
help the queen i can stop corvex
sorry excuse me
excuse me
stop stop
who's what's that
it's all right that's muzzy
he's a friend mozzie
this is the queen your majesty
what's happening what's that green thing
oh that's not a thing that's
muzzy he's a friend but he can't help
where's corvex ah yes
korvax can help korvax is
clever no he isn't he's silly
i can help your majesty you
but you aren't clever i am
[Music]
lovely what are you doing
a moment
what are you doing excuse me
i'm hungry hungry
but the king's in there why are you
eating that
because i like it
ah i see
this goes here
oh no it doesn't careful please muzzy
it's all right it goes in here
and this goes in
[Music]
here
all right your majesty i'm ready
i'm ready too it's hot in here
[Music]
ah oh that's better
thank you mozzie you are clever
where's bob bob bob the gardener
oh look
[Music]
all oh
okay we've got him
corvex corvex wake up
why what's happening
who are you where am i
why am i here who am i
you are corvax and you are silly
yes i'm silly
no i'm not i'm clever
you are not clever corvex
take him away
yes take him away
[Laughter]
oh
stand there now
try this
they're going they're going into the
[Music]
computer
a black and white one too lots and lots
of silvias
coming back this way three chairs for
marcy
[Music]
there goes number three number two
and number one and that leaves
[Music]
who is that beautiful girl what is her
name
where does she come from when can i see
her
[Music]
why am i down here
now we are together
i love you
that goes in there this goes up here
i don't like this job
that one this one no
the big one oh dear oh dear
oh dear
[Music]
now for that one this and that one
daddy job
now it's lunchtime yes i'm hungry
take all those away oh dear oh
dear oh dear
now i'm in my spaceship now i'm going
away
thank you thank you muzzy please come
back someday
goodbye goodbye goodbye
we're saying goodbye to mazzy we're
saying goodbye to you
the king the queen
sylvia bob corvex and norman
[Music]
goodbye