[Music]
until i run for mr jack stack
i'm his secretary okay
same here
have a good day thanks
okay
good afternoon nadine hi did you have a
nice lunch
no i didn't i went to an italian
restaurant in north beach
and i ate too much
[Music]
do we have anything for a stomachache oh
look
[Music]
here you are thanks
oh i forgot you received a telegram
a telegram when it came a few minutes
ago
what do we have here let me guess
a strange message from an old friend
in an exotic country nadine your
intuition is amazing
[Music]
jack of hearts remember me
i found the captain's gold can finally
pay you
but need your help signed
steve wilde island of barbudas
what does it mean trouble
people bring me lots of problems big
problems little problems but this
is not my kind of problem
who's steve wild he's an old friend
we worked together in the merchant
marines we sailed from maine to mexico
and from mexico to cairo
those were the good old days not exactly
we drank too much and played too many
card games
poker that's right he lost
and he couldn't pay me then he
disappeared
the last time i saw him was about 20
years ago
a ghost from the past day
let me see the telegram
jack of hearts is your nickname
nadine you're a very good detective
he says i found the captain's gold
what is the captain's gold i don't know
and i'm not interested this is not
my kind of problem
nadine you answer it
it's always for you
hello a long distance phone call from mr
jack stark
speaking i'll connect you
be careful mr stark
stay away from steve wilde
don't come to the island of barbudos
who is that i don't know
but i know one thing what's that we're
leaving on the first plane to barbudas
make the reservations
are you taking me with you well
you did a fantastic job on the last case
you have good luck
okay jack
but i want to be your partner
i don't want to be your secretary
[Music]
my partner are you serious
yes i am
okay try your luck
cut the cards
high card wins
queen of diamonds
[Music]
jack of hearts you win you're not a
secretary
now we're partners so let's get to work
where's the atlas it's on the shelf
where's barbudos
look here it is it's southeast
of florida between cuba and haiti
[Music]
tell me more about your friend steve
wilde
he was born in new york his parents were
poor his father was a factory worker so
he didn't earn
very much money there were seven
children in the family so
life was hard yeah
he went to school and he worked at the
same time
he joined the merchant marines when he
was 18.
did you meet him in the merchant marines
write again partner
the island of barbudos offers a
marvelous
opportunity for tourists captain kidd
once hidden its mountains he was a
famous
pirate captain kid watched the spanish
ships
from devil's rock you can take a boat
trip
and see devil's rock
ladies and gentlemen we are now entering
the bermuda triangle
in 1958 a dc-3 was flying from florida
to the bahama islands
[Applause]
[Music]
now practice
this is the operator can i help you
what's your telephone number
sorry i can't hear you would you repeat
that
what number are you calling
i'll connect you
who's steve wild he's an old friend
we worked together in the merchant
marines we sailed from
maine to mexico and from mexico to cairo
those were the good old days not exactly
we drank too much and played too many
card games
poker that's right he lost
and he couldn't pay me then he
disappeared
the last time i saw him was 20 years ago
[Music]
me
kill the
[Music]
around
are you looking for something
where is the gold ring
it's in my jacket pocket
give me my jacket
slowly
[Music]
work all night till the morning
it smells good here wow
that was a long trip jack
you look just the same hello steve
well not exactly who's this
i'd like to introduce you to nadine
she's my sec
my new partner welcome to barbudos
let me uh take your bag i can
carry it
taxi
waterfront hotel
americans season your 20
okay
when did you come to barbudo steve about
20 years ago i left the merchant marines
first i worked on fishing boats then i
saved enough money to buy a boat
did you buy a fishing boat no
i didn't i bought an excursion boat
it has glass windows you can see the
tropical fish under the water
i take tourists around the island we go
to
sunny beaches they go swimming
it's not an exciting life but the island
is beautiful
the food is delicious and the people are
friendly
am i boring you jack no you're not
i'm a professional listener it sounds
like you found your island paradise
steve
and i found the captain's gold
what is the captain's gold
be patient
you had a long trip why don't you rest
then meet me at my boat good idea
where is it walk one block down to the
port
and turn left the glass boat
right we'll meet you in an hour
see you later alligator
hi
mr stark and his partner are staying at
the waterfront hotel
they're going to meet steve on his boat
in an hour
good i hid a microphone on that boat
last night
see you in an hour jack have a rest
thanks are you having fun
yes it's a great adventure
but your friend's a little strange
he was a little strange 20 years ago
[Music]
now practice
these flowers are nice
they smell nice
this hotel is old it looks
old
that music is loud
it sounds loud
[Music]
this chocolate is sweet it tastes
sweet
these flowers are soft
they feel soft
what's your name steve wild
where are you from i'm from new york
when did you come to barbudos about 20
years ago
do you like it here yes i do
the island is beautiful food is
delicious
and the people are friendly
steve wild
i'm from new york
about 20 years ago
yes i do the island is beautiful
food is delicious and the people are
friendly
[Music]
i had a mysterious visitor last night as
i was out enjoying the night life
a woman came into my room you always had
trouble with women steve
when i got back she was hiding behind
the door
i tried to stop her but she escaped
i think she was looking for the
captain's gold
listen steve we understood your telegram
except the captain's gold
what are you talking about captain kidd
you're kidding no i'm not i'm serious
i found his skull and a strange
gold ring
a few days ago i made a fascinating
discovery
i was taking some tourists around the
island went to a cove
as i was looking through the glass i saw
something strange
i returned the next day and jumped into
the water
i swam down about 20 feet
and found this skull i was looking at it
when i noticed something shiny it was
this gold ring you brought us
all the way to our buddhists for this
to be or not to be
that is the question why do you think
it's the skull of captain kidd
because i took it to an expert it's 200
years old
i'm telling you it's captain kidd skull
and the ring is pure gold
be careful it's broken
it's not broken it's an earring
a pirate's earring this is getting more
interesting jack look at the writing
inside
the letters look like bones i think it's
a code
they're not letters they're numbers
roman numerals you see steve but you
don't
observe 23
73 maybe
their latitude in longitude lines
that's it the coordinates
they indicate a beach it's 15 miles
north
of saint augustine i found the ring
very near there you two
are amazing
teamwork
two heads are better than one
[Music]
now practice
what's your name luis rodriguez
are you married yes i have a pretty wife
do you have any children yes we do
we have a girl and a little boy a
daughter and a son
how old are they our daughters six
and our sons too
luis rodriguez
yes i have a pretty wife
yes we do we have a girl and a little
boy
a daughter and a son
our daughters six and our sons too
while steve was out last night i hid a
microphone on his boat
when i was looking for the gold ring
steve came back
so i hid behind a door as
i was leaving he tried to stop me
but i escaped
i'm serious i found his skull
and a strange gold ring
a few days ago i made a fascinating
discovery
i was taking some tourists around the
island we went to a cove
as i was looking through the glass i saw
something strange
i returned the next day and jumped into
the water
[Music]
this is the place right on top of this
rock
or under it
i can't move it will help
come on nadine push
oh this is just like treasure island
we're going to be rich what's inside
the captain's telescope
i can't see anything i'll clean it
let's go back to the boat
they're going to take us straight to the
treasure
then we'll take it from them
look at this
it's a map of the island what does the
message
say look and you will find
at midnight on the devil's throne
listen to the devil's moan
it's a riddle look and you will
find that's from the bible saint luke
chapter 11 verse 9.
how do you know that i'm a detective
remember
[Music]
listen midnight is 12 o'clock on a map
that means north it's a
clue start at midnight
means start in the north
but where in the north at the north pole
the devil's throne
wait a minute there's a place called
devil's rock
captain kidd watched the spanish ships
from
devil's rock where is it
here on the island from the north end
how far is it from here 11 miles north
nine miles west chapter 11
verse nine bingo
[Music]
so
lucky i stopped smoking
i'm going to stop soon
look it's the devil's throne
look and you will find
start at midnight on the devil's throne
listen to the devil's moon
who's the devil captain kid
listen
the devil's moan just the wind
[Music]
look and you will find
anybody home
[Music]
just a few bats we'll need flashlights
come on
be careful
this is it eureka
we're finally going to find the treasure
with
a little help from los americanos
[Laughter]
what was that the devil's laugh
don't worry no one saw us come in here
and no one's going to see you leave
keep working don't move oh shoot the
same old steve you always
were cheat you needed our
help and now you're going to leave us
here and take the gold
just like a pirate be quiet
and keep digging i'm digging my own
[Music]
grave
open it
go and choose
i don't think you're going to enjoy this
treasure
steve this treasures belongs to the
people of barbudos
take him away come on let's go
i recognize your voice
you telephoned me in san francisco
an expensive telephone call who are you
[Music]
maria moreno government agent island of
barbados
what are you going to do with us i'm
going to send you back
to san francisco
[Music]
[Applause]
now practice
are you a taxi driver no i'm not
i'm a government agent what are you
going to do with steve
oh we are going to let him go free
why because you won't testify against
him
no i'm not i'm a government agent
oh we are going to let him go free
[Music]
well the vacation's over
did you enjoy your visit to the island
of barbudas mr stark
the island of barbudos offers some
marvelous
opportunity for tourists why did they
name
it barbudos well i'll tell you
a long time ago it was called sugar
island
when the english came to the island they
burned the forest
and planted sugarcane then what happened
the sugar cane destroyed the land then
english pirates used the island
pirates like captain kidd why did they
use
this island because spanish ships sailed
by here
they carried gold and silver from the
mines in mexico
when was that about
200 years ago so captain kid robbed the
spanish ships
how much is the treasure worth several
million dollars what are you going to do
with the money
the government of barbudos will build
school
and hospitals
so why did they name the island barbudas
oh sorry i forgot to tell you
but means bearded men in spanish
the spanish sailors called pirates
barbudos
that's right
[Music]
thank you both for all your help
our pleasure how are you going to
pay for your trip that's a good question
maybe this will help the gold ring
the pirate's earring bon voyage mr
[Music]
adios
what are they going to do with steve
they're going to let him go free
why because i won't testify against him
he is a liar and a thief
but i don't think he's really dangerous
jack of hearts
oh i have something for you
a souvenir
i don't wear earrings
thanks partner
[Music]
now practice
you're an agent aren't you yes i am
do you like your job yes i do
where did you go to school i studied
in the united states in miami
when did you leave school i left school
about 10 years ago
when did you become an agent i became an
agent after i left school
yes i am
yes i do
i studied in the united states in miami
i left school about 10 years ago
i became an agent after i left school