chapter one Mowgli's brothers one very
warm evening in the Sione Hills in
southern India father wolf woke up from
his days rest next to him lay mother
wolf with their four cubs beside her
it's time to look for food said father
wolf and he stood up to leave the cave
good luck said a voice
it was the jackal taboc we who eats
everything and anything even pieces of
old clothes from the villages the Wolves
of India do not like him because he runs
around making trouble and telling bad
stories about them Shere Khan the tiger
is coming to look for food here said
Tabak we he can't cried fie the wolf by
the law of the jungle he must tell us
first before he comes here to hunt xie
khan has a bad leg so he can kill only
cows in the village near him the people
are angry that is why he is coming here
to start hunting in a new place listen
you can hear him now said taboc we he is
a stupid animal
said father wolf and he listened to the
angry noise of a tiger who has not eaten
no one will find anything to eat in the
jungle now but Shere Khan is hunting man
not animal tonight said taboc we the law
of the jungle says that animals must not
hunt man because man killing brings men
with guns then everybody in the jungle
is in danger father and mother wolf
listened to Shere Khan in the jungle not
far away
then suddenly they heard a noise much
nearer to them it's a man a man's cub
look said father wolf and there in front
of them stood a baby who could just walk
he looked up at father wolf and laughed
is that a man's cub asked mother wolf I
have never seen one bring it here
the baby small and with no clothes
pushed its way between the Cubs to get
near to mother wolf look she said he is
taking his meal with the others I have
heard that this
has happened before said father wolf but
I have never seen it until now look at
him he is not afraid suddenly it was
dark and xie Khan was pushing his great
head in through the mouth of the cave we
are pleased that you visit us Shere Khan
said father wolf but his eyes were angry
what do you need I am hunting a man's
cub said Shia Khan
its father and mother have run away give
it to me
father wolf knew that Shia Khan could
not get inside the cave because he was
too big the man's cub belongs to us he
said the pack the other wolves and I
will decide if we want to kill him we
will kill him
not you the man's cub belongs to me it
is I
Shere Khan who speaks and Shia calms
roar filled the cave with noise no came
the angry voice of mother wolf the man's
cub belongs to me we will not kill him
he will live to run with the other
wolves to be my son now go away
fish killer eater of Cubs go
Shaya Khan went he knew that he could
not fight
mother wolf in the cave but I will have
this man-cub one day you thieves he
shouted from the jungle do you really
want to keep him
mother said father wolf keep him said
mother wolf yes he came here by night
alone and hungry but he was not afraid
yes I will keep him and I will call him
Mowgli the Frog but what will the other
wolves of the pack say by the law of the
jungle all Wolf Cubs must come to the
pack when they can walk the Wolves look
at the Cubs carefully then the Cubs are
free to run anywhere because all the
adult wolves know them and will not
attack them when the four Wolf Cubs
could run a little father wolf took them
and Mowgli and mother wolf to the
meeting Rock here the hundred wolves of
the Wolfpack met every month when the
moon was full the leader of the pack was
our kala a great gray wolf
each new wolf cub came to stand in front
of him and our Kayla said look well o
wolves look well at the end father wolf
pushed mouthed Lea into the circle of
wolves
then from the trees outside the circle
they heard the voice of Shere Khan the
man-cub belongs to me give him to me
akela did not move but said only look
well who speaks for this man-cub two
voices who are not his father and mother
must speak for him there is only one
other animal who can come to these wolf
meetings Baloo the sleepy brown bear his
job is to teach the law of the jungle to
the wolf cubs I speak for the man cub
came Baloo's deep voice let him run with
the pack I myself will teach him we need
another voice to speak for him said
akela silently another animal jumped
down into the circle it was Bar gira the
Panther black as the night clever strong
and dangerous o our kala will you let me
speak said Bagheera softly the law of
the jungle
says it is possible to buy the life of a
cop
it is bad to kill a man-cub he cannot
hurt you let him live with you and I
will give you a fat cow newly killed
which lies in the jungle not far away
the voices of the wolves replied let him
live
they were always hungry and they wanted
to get the dead cow soon they went away
and there were only our kala Bagheera
Baloo and Mowgli's wolf family left they
could hear the angry roars of Shere Khan
in the night it is good said akela men
are clever
perhaps this man-cub will help us when
he is older take him away he said to
father wolf and teach him well and so
because of Baloo's good word and the
present of a cow Mowgli now belonged to
the Sione Wolf Pack the story of
Mowgli's life among the wolves fills
many books but we must jump ten or
eleven years now
father wolf Baloo and Bagheera taught
Mowgli well and he learned everything
about the jungle he knew the meaning of
every sound in the trees of every song
of the birds of every splash in the
water he learnt to climb trees like a
monkey
to swim in the rivers like a fish and to
hunt for his food as cleverly as any
animal in the jungle
chapter 2 the monkey-people
bar loo the old brown bear loved
teaching Mowgli
he taught him how to speak to the
different jungle people and he taught
him the important master words but
Mowgli sometimes got bored with all the
lessons one day when he was not
listening Baloo hit him very softly on
the head and Mowgli ran away angrily
Bagheera the Black Panther was not happy
about this remember how small he is he
said to Baloo
how can his little head hold all your
long words these words we keep him safe
from the birds from the snake people and
all the animals that hunt said Baloo it
is true that he is only small but no one
will hurt him if he remembers all the
master words come my ugly he called into
the trees come and say the words again
Mowgli climbed down from a tree and came
to sit next to them I will say the words
to bar guerra not you fat old Baloo he
said crossly
very well said Baloo sadly say the words
for the hunting people we are of one
blood you and I said Mowgli good now for
the birds
Mowgli said the same words but with the
sound of a bird now for the snake people
said Baloo
Mowgli then made the long sound which
was like no other noise only the noise
of a snake good said Baloo gently one
day you will thank me for my lessons now
you will be safe in the jungle because
no snake no bird no animal will hurt you
you do not need to be afraid of anyone
and I shall have my people and go with
them high up in the trees shouted Mowgli
what did you say Mowgli asked Baloo
surprised have you been with the
bandar-log the monkey people Mowgli
could hear that Baloo was angry and he
saw to that Bagheera's green eyes were
cold and hard
when Baloo hurt my head said Mowgli I
went away and the grey monkeys came down
from the trees and talked to me they
were kind to me and gave me nice things
to eat then they took me up into the
trees they said that I was their brother
and they wanted me to be their leader
one day why have you never told me about
the monkey people bad old Baloo they
play all day and don't do lessons
and I will play with them again
listen man-cub said baloo angrily i have
taught you the law for all the jungle
people but not for the monkey people
they have no law their ways are not our
ways they are noisy and dirty and they
think that they are a great people but
then they forget everything the rest of
the jungle people do not talk to them or
even think about them remember what I
tell you now Glee listened and was sorry
but all this time the bandar-log were
above them in the trees listening and
watching
they followed Mowgli and his friends
through the jungle until it was time for
the midday rest
Mowgli lay between his friends and went
to sleep
saying I will never talk to or play with
the monkey people again when he woke up
he was high in a tree and there were
hands holding his legs and arms hard
strong little hands down below Baloo was
shouting angrily and Bagheera was trying
to climb up the tree but he was too
heavy for the thin branches the monkeys
shouting and laughing carried Mowgli
between them and began their journey
along the monkey roads which are high in
the trees
it was a wild exciting journey
the
he's jumped from treetop to treetop
crashing through the leaves and branches
at first Mowgli was afraid of falling
but then he began to think he must tell
Baloo and Bagheera where he was high up
in the blue sky he saw chil the kite the
Big Bird saw that the monkeys were
carrying a man-cub
he flew down to look and was surprised
to hear the bird call of the kites we
are of one blood you and I who are you
called chill Mowgli the man-cub came the
reply watch where they take me and tell
Baloo and Bagheera
I will cold chill and he flew high above
the trees and watched with his
far-seeing eyes monkeys can travel fast
when they want to and by now Baloo and
Bagheera what a long way behind we
cannot follow the bandar-log through the
trees said Baloo and we will never catch
them but they are afraid of ah the big
Python he can climb as easily as the
monkeys and he eats them perhaps he will
help us and so Baloo and Bagheera went
to look for car the Python they found
him lying in the Sun ten
of brown and yellow snake beautiful and
dangerous watch news cult car when he
saw them we are looking for food said
baloo he knew that you must not hurry
car he is too big
let me come with you said car hungrily I
have not eaten for days we are following
the bandar-log said baloo those noisy
dirty thieves have stolen our man-cub
and we love our man-cub very much the
bandar-log said Bagheera cleverly are
very much afraid of you car but they say
bad things about you and call you old
yellow fish I hear sidqa I will teach
them not to call me bad names where did
they take your man-cub they will be
tired of him quickly and that is bad for
him up up look up Baloo Baloo looked up
and saw chil the kind high in the sky
what is it called Baloo
I have seen Mowgli the man-cub with the
bandar-log he knew the master word they
have taken him to the monkey City the
lost
City baloo and bagheera
new of the monkey city men lived there
once but they left hundreds of years ago
nobody went there now only the
bandar-log we must leave at once
said bagheera it is a long way I will
come as fast as I can said Baloo but you
and car can go faster I will follow you
the lost city was very old
there were many beautiful buildings but
the walls were broken and full of holes
and there were tall trees in houses that
were now open to the sky the monkey
people called the place their City and
ran around everywhere
inland out of the empty houses up and
down the fruit trees in the old gardens
now Mowgli was in their City and the
monkey people were very pleased with
themselves
this boy can help us they said he can
teach us how to make things because men
are clever with their hands but monkeys
make many plans and always forget them
five minutes later
when Mowgli arrived in the city he was
tired and hungry bring me food he said
and twenty or thirty monkeys ran to
bring him fruit but they started
fighting and forgot to take any fruit
back to Mowgli Mowgli knew that he was
in a bad place
Ballu was right he thought the
bandar-log have no law and their ways
are not our ways I must try to get away
Baloo will surely be angry with me but
that is better than life with the
bandar-log but when Mowgli went to the
walls of the city the monkeys pulled him
back you are very happy here with us we
are great we are wonderful we all say so
and so it is true they shouted don't
they ever sleep thought Mowgli he looked
up at the sky there's a cloud coming
over the moon
perhaps I can run away when it's dark
but I am tired
Chapter three
Karl's hunting
Bagheera and car were also watching that
cloud
they were now outside the city walls but
they knew they had to be careful there
were only two of them and there were
hundreds of monkeys they are over there
by that house talking about the boy said
Bagheera when the cloud hides the moon I
will attack them I will go to the higher
ground at the west war Cassatt and come
down the hill very fast
good hunting the Black Panther ran
quickly to the crowds of monkeys and
started hitting right and left as hard
as he could
the monkeys screamed angrily but then
one of them shouted there is only one
here kill him kill and a crowd of
monkeys jumped on Bagheera biting and
pulling another group pulled Mowgli up a
wall and pushed him over he fell down
into a dark room which had no doors or
windows and he could not get out stay
there
shouted the monkeys until we have killed
your friend and then we will play with
you if the snakes leave you alive Mowgli
and he seems
in the darkness around him we are of one
blood you and I he said quickly giving
the snakes call the snakes replied we
will not bite you but stand still little
brother because your feet can hurt us
Mowgli stood very still and listened to
the fight around Bagheera for the first
time ever the big Panther was fighting
for his life
then Mowgli remembered something there
was a big tank of water near one of the
buildings go to the tank Bagheera get to
the water
Bagheera heard and he knew that Mowgli
was safe
suddenly he felt stronger and he pulled
himself slowly to the tank fighting
against the crowds of monkeys
then Baloo came running in from the
jungle shouting Bagheera I am here at
once the monkeys jumped on him and the
bear started to hit them with his great
strong arms
Mowgli heard a splash when Bagheera
jumped into the tank the monkeys were
afraid of water and could not follow him
there but they stood all round the sides
ready to jump on him if he tried to get
out and help Baloo and where was car all
this time it was a hard climb up to the
west wall and car moved carefully over
the stones now he came down the hill
very quickly hungry and wanting to kill
car was 10 meters long heavy and strong
he went silently into the crowd of
monkeys around Baloo and he did not need
to hit twice when they are very young
monkeys are told about car the silent
thief who can kill the strongest monkey
all monkeys are afraid of car now they
ran with shouts of its car run run then
car opened his mouth for the first time
and spoke one long hissing word the
monkeys was suddenly
silent and still and nothing moved in
the city Bagheera
pulled himself out of the tank get the
man-cub out and let us go he said I
can't fight anymore and the monkeys will
attack us again they will not move until
I tell them to move said Karr we must
thank you car we could not do it without
you said Baloo I am happy to help where
is the man-cub said car here in this
room but I cannot get out
take him away called the snakes around
Mowgli he dances around too much and he
will stand on us stand back man-cub said
car I will break the wall with two
meters of his heavy body off the ground
car hit the wall very hard five or six
times a hole opened and Mowgli jumped
quickly through it he ran and put his
arms around Baloo and Bagheera are you
hurt
asked Baloo not much said Mowgli but the
bandar-log have hurt you badly my
friends it is nothing said Baloo but you
must thank car he has done much for you
tonight
Mowgli turned and saw the head of the
great python so
oh this is the man-cub said car he is
like the bandar-log but not the same
be careful man-cub that I do not make a
mistake when I am hunting monkeys we are
of one blood you and I
Mowgli answered you have given me my
life tonight when I kill it will be for
you if you are hungry well spoken said
Baloo
you are brave young man said Karr and
you speak well now go with your friends
the moon is going down you must not see
what will happen here next car went
softly out in front of the lines of City
monkeys and began to dance his head
moved from right to left and his long
body turned this way and that way making
circles that changed every second slowly
never hurrying car danced in front of
the monkeys Baloo and Bagheera stood and
could not move Maui was and did not
understand band her log said the deep
voice of car at last
can you move without
word from you car we cannot move kamila
to me said car the lines of monkeys came
nearer and Baloo and Bagheera walked
forward to Nia hissed car and they all
moved forward again loudly put his hands
on Baloo and Bagheera to get them away
and the two animals woke up keep your
hand on me
Mowgli whispered Bagheera or I will go
back to car and walk into his mouth it's
only old car dancing said Mowgli let us
go and the three of them went away into
the jungle a pythons dance is dangerous
to watch said Baloo even for us car will
have good hunting tonight and now Mowgli
said Bagheera angrily Baloo and I have
fought hard for you the monkeys have
bitten us and pulled us and hit us and
all this man-cub was because you played
with the bandar-log it is true said
Mowgli sadly I am a bad man cub the law
of the jungle says we must punish you
said Bagheera Baloo was happy that
Mowgli was safe and with them again but
he could not speak against the law it is
right
to punish me said Mowgli I did wrong
Bagheera hit him very softly for a
panther but very heavily for a little
boy Mowgli did not cry now said Bagheera
jump on my back little brother and we
will go home one of the good things
about jungle law is that after you were
punished the matter is finished
chapter four the fight of the rock
Mowgli always went to the meetings of
the Wolfpack and there he learned
something new one day if he looked hard
at any wolf the wolf could not meet his
eyes and looked away
Mowgli thought this was funny he did not
understand that he was different from
the wolves all the jungle people were
his friends but not sheer Khan of course
mother wolf told him that the tiger
wanted to kill him one day you must kill
Shere Khan if you don't kill him he will
kill you but Mowgli forgot he was only a
boy not a wolf
Shaya Khan's still came often to that
part of the jungle are kala was older
now and not so strong and Shere Khan
made friends with some of the younger
wolves our kala could not stop them and
Shiah Khan began to make trouble for
Mowgli I hear you can't look into the
mancubs eyes he said laughing to the
young wolves and the young wolves began
to get angry Bagheera who had eyes and
ears everywhere
knew something of this and told Mowgli
Mowgli laughed but Bagheera went on open
your eyes little brother remember that
our kala is old and he will not always
be the leader of the pack Shere Khan has
taught the younger wolves
but a man-cub has no place with them and
soon you will be a man not a man-cub but
the wolves are my brothers why will they
want to send me away look at me said
Bagheera and Mowgli looked at him hard
between the eyes
the big black cat turned his head away
quickly that is why he said not even I
can look in your eyes that is why they
want to kill you you are clever you are
a man I did not know these things said
Mowgli quietly now listen the day will
soon come when our kala cannot kill his
deer in the hunt then at the next
meeting of the pack the younger wolves
will be against our kala and against you
when that time comes go to the men's
houses in the village and take some of
their red flower that will be a stronger
friend to you than I or Baloo the red
flower was fire all animals are afraid
of it and do not call it by its name I
will get some said Mowgli I will go and
get it now and keep it ready and he ran
through the jungle to the village on his
way he heard the sounds of the Wolfpack
hunting a big deer show us that you are
strong our kala came the voices of the
young
wolves kill it Mowgli stopped and
listened and he could hear that our kala
did not kill the deer so the time has
come already he thought and hurried to
the village he watched and waited and
soon he saw a child who was carrying a
fire pot Mowgli jumped up took the pot
from him and quickly ran away back to
the jungle all that day he kept his fire
alive with leaves and pieces of wood in
the evening taboc we came and told him
that the Wolves wanted him at the
meeting
Mowgli laughed and went when he arrived
he saw that our kala was not in his
special place on top of the rock but
beside it that meant that another wolf
could try to take our Kayla's place she
akong was there too with all the younger
wolves around him Mowgli sat down with
the firebot between his legs
Bagheera lay beside him Shere Khan began
to speak and Mowgli jumped up Free
People is Sher Khan your leader does a
tiger belong in the Wolf Pack there is
no wolf on the rock began Shere Khan but
the other wolf said let our kala speak
our kala looked up old and
free people I have been your leader for
many years in all that time no wolf has
died in the hunt but this time I did not
kill my dear the law of the jungle says
that you can kill me now but the law
also says that you must come one by one
no one spoke our kala was old but nobody
wanted to fight our kala alone
then she accom
oak bah this old wolf is not important
he will die soon
it is the man-cub who has lived too long
give him to me a man a man cried most of
the younger wolves angrily a man does
not belong in the Wolfpack my ugly is
our brother said akela he has eaten all
food he has slept with us he has done
nothing wrong
let him go to his own place he is a man
cried Shia Khan and most of the Wolves
Mowgli
stood up the fire-pot in his hands he
was very angry and very sad you have
said many times that I am a man I was
your brother but I
not call you my brothers again I will
decide on my life or my death not you I
am a man and to show you I have brought
the red flower with me he dropped the
firebot on the ground and some of the
fire fell out the wolves were very
afraid and moved back Mowgli held a long
piece of wood in the fire and the end
began to burn brightly you are the
leader now said Bagheera softly help are
kala
he was always your friend good said
Mowgli he looked at the frightened
wolves I go from you to my people the
world of men but first and Mowgli went
to chacon this killer of cows wanted to
kill me this is what men do to killers
of cows and he hit Shere Khan on the
head with the burning stick the tiger
was very frightened go now said Mowgli
to Shere Khan the next time I come to
this rock it will be with your dead body
I tell you this also my brothers you
will not kill our kala because I do not
want that our kala is free to live and
Mowgli jumped at the young wolves with
his burning stick and they all ran away
in the end there were only Ark
Bagheera and a few older wolves left
then something began to hurt my ugly
inside him and for the first time in his
life tears ran down his face what is it
what is it am i dying
Bagheera no little brother
you are a man and these are men's tears
but you must go the jungle is closed to
you now yes said Mowgli
I will go to men but first I must say
goodbye to my mother and he went to the
cave and cried on mother Wolf's coat you
will not forget me my ugly said to his
wolf family never said his wolf brothers
come to the foot of the hill when you
are a man and we will talk with you come
soon little frog said father wolf
because your mother and I are getting
old I will surely come set my ugly and I
will bring the coat of Shere Khan and
put it on the meeting rock and in the
morning Mowgli went down the hill alone
to meet those strange things that are
called men
Chapter five
Tyler Tiger Mowgli's ooh that he had
enemies now and he went far away he ran
until he came to a village in a place
with many rocks and narrow valleys
everywhere mouth Lee could see cows and
buffaloes some little boys were looking
after the cows but when they saw Mowgli
they shouted and ran away
Mowgli walked on until he came to the
village he sat down by the gate when a
man came out of the village Mowgli
opened his mouth to show that he wanted
food the man ran back into the village
and came back with a hundred other
people they all looked at mao glee and
saw the bite marks on his arms and legs
look said a man those are the bite marks
of wolves he is a wolf child who has run
away from the jungle he is a
good-looking boy said one of the women
messua he looks like your little boy
that was taken by the tiger let me look
said Masuya yes he is thin but he looks
like my son take him to your house
mizuha the villager said the jungle took
your boy and the jungle has given you
this one back
woman called masseur took my ugly to her
house and gave him milk and bread
this was Mowgli's first time in a house
and he did not like it it felt like a
prison but I am a man now he thought and
I must do what men do I must also learn
to speak like men he knew all the many
languages of the jungle and so it was
easy for him to learn the sounds of men
that first evening he learned many words
from masseur but that night he did not
want to sleep inside the house so he
climbed out of the window and went to
sleep in a field near the village before
he went to sleep a soft grey nose
touched his face it was grey brother the
eldest of mother Wolf's Cubs wake little
brother he said I bring news Xie Kahn
has gone away you burned his coat with
the red flower but he says that when he
comes back he will kill you
I remember also what I said about Shere
Khan said Mowgli but it is good to have
news will you always bring me news gray
brother yes little brother but you will
not forget that you are a wolf you will
not forget us when you are with men
never replied Mowgli I will always
remember that I love you all for three
Mowgli learned how to be like a man he
had to wear clothes learn how to use
money and how to work in the fields in
the evenings he sat with the villagers
under a great tree while the men told
stories about the jungle and the animals
once when Buldeo the village hunter told
a story about a tiger
Mowgli had to hide his face because he
was laughing at the end he said full day
of stories are stupid he knows nothing
about the jungle the villagers did not
like this and after that they sent
Mowgli out every day with the other boys
to look after the herds of cows and
buffaloes while they ate Mowgli enjoyed
this work and usually went on alone with
a big group of cows and buffaloes one
day he saw a grey brother under a tree
near the jungle
Shaya khan has come back but he is
hiding for a while then he is coming to
kill you said gray brother
very good said Mowgli tell me when he
comes meet me at the river by the big
dark tree with golden flowers I will
watch for you there every day day after
day Mowgli went out with the herds but
there was nobody at the dock tree then
at last the day came when grey brother
was waiting for him
Shaya khan has
it for a month and is hoping that you
have now forgotten about him said the
wolf he's going to wait for you at the
village gate this evening but now he is
hiding in a big dry ravine of the
waingunga I met Tabak we this morning
here gray brother showed his teeth a
little and before I broke his back he
told me all about Shearer Khan's plan as
Shere Khan eaten today or does he hunt
empty the answer was life or death for
Mowgli he killed and ate this morning
and he has drunk too how stupid he is
said Mowgli does he think that I shall
wait until he has slept he stood and
thought for a while the ravine of wine
Ganga I can take the Buffaloes round to
the top end and chase Shere Khan down
the ravine after a meal he cannot fight
or climb easily but I need a big group
of cows at the bottom end of the ravine
to stop him escaping then we will catch
him between the Buffaloes and the cows
can you help me gray brother not hai
alone said gray brother but I have
someone who will help me and the big
gray head of our kala came out from the
trees are kala kala said Mowgli I knew
you would not forget me the two wolves
ran here and there and
the herd and soon the cows and buffaloes
were in two groups
already they were getting excited and
dangerous the other herd boys who were
watching a long way away ran back to the
village with the news keep the cows
together gray brother called Mowgli
drive them into the bottom end of the
ravine and keep them there until we come
down our kala you and I will take the
Buffaloes
round to the top they drove the
Buffaloes round in a big circle uphill
it took a long time because they did not
want Shere Khan to hear them at last
Mowgli was ready he stopped and shouted
down the ravine Shere Khan it is I
Mowgli
it is time for our meeting Mowgli rode
on the back of Rama the biggest of the
Buffaloes and our kala chased the herd
from behind the Buffaloes began to run
down the ravine faster and faster and
the ground shook under their heavy feet
sheer Khan heard the noise and woke up
he knew what it was and he began to run
down the ravine no Tiger can hope to
stand against a herd of buffaloes when
they are moving fast he looked for a way
to escape but the ravine was narrow with
high rocky walls he had to go on heavy
with his dinner and his drink then
he saw the cows at the bottom of the
ravine and turned but it was too late he
fell owned of a feat of the Buffaloes
and they ran over him like a river
running down a mountain the Buffaloes
did not stop until they crashed into the
herd of cows Mowgli
jumped off Rama's back and shouted to
our kala and gray brother it is done
Shia Khan is dead he died the death of a
dog not a fighting Tiger loudly took his
knife and started to cut the coat from
shere Khan's body it was hard work
after an hour Mowgli was still working
when suddenly he felt a hand on his back
it was bull Deo the village hunter go
and look after your buffaloes he cried
angrily I will take this Tigers coat I
can sell it for a hundred rupees and you
can have one rupee for yourself
no said Mowgli
I need this coat listen boy shouted bull
do I am the village hunter and I will
take the coat and keep all the money
then mowgli spoke to our kala in the
wolf language and suddenly bull Deo was
lying on his back on the ground with a
big gray wolf standing over him
bull dale said Mowgli for a long time
this tiger has won
to kill me but I have killed him Buldeo
was very afraid who was this boy who
could talk to wolves and kill Tigers
great king he said to Mowgli I am an old
man I thought you were just a herd boy
let me go now and I will go away go and
peace go with you replied Mowgli and he
went on with his work it was nearly dark
when at last he and the Wolves pulled
the great coat away from the Tigers body
now we must hide this and take the cows
and the Buffaloes back to the village
said Mowgli but when Mowgli came near
the village there was a crowd of people
waiting for him at the gate
go away wolf child they shouted go away
or we will kill you Mowgli did not
understand she akan the tiger who killed
cows and stole children was dead but
people were angry with him he turned
away and looked up at the stars in the
sky no more sleeping in houses for me
akela let us get shear Khan's coat and
go away the moon climbed high in the sky
and the frightened villagers watched
while Mowgli began to run across the
fields with the two gray wolves running
at his side
the moon was going down when Mowgli and
the two wolves came to mother Wolf's
cave the men do not want me mother
called Mowgli I have come home and I
have brought the coat of Shere Khan
mother wolf came out of the cave very
happy to see Mowgli again and to know
that she akan was dead from the jungle
came the deep voice of Bagheera little
brother we are pleased to see you then
Mowgli took the coat of Shere Khan and
put it on the great rock at the Wolves
meeting place are kala lay on it and
cold look well o wolves and the wolf
pack came and looked and saw that sheer
Khan was dead now said Mowgli I do not
belong to the wolf pack or to the man
pack I will hunt alone in the jungle and
we will hunt with you said gray brother
and the rest of mother Wolf's Cubs and
Mowgli went away into the jungle and
lived and hunted with his brothers the
Wolves