[Music]
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
[Applause]
so
mmm
[Music]
[Applause]
you all know the lovely old legend of
beauty and the beast
i used to be the law around here sheriff
otto they called me
and i knew the beast and i'm telling you
that what really happened
was far far more terrifying than
anything the storytellers
ever admitted it started in the royal
palace
where king maximilian lay dying
ring me
my song
bring me i
saw
your son died at birth your majesty many
years ago
you have to choose a successor
and choose from among those present your
majesty
us your noble relatives
word with your cousin
you and i are leading contenders for the
throne i
am the leading contender count rudolph
you were just
one ambitious noble among many
so you wouldn't consider perhaps forming
an alliance
maybe working together i know you too
well cousin you're mean
vicious and cruel and ruthless
you forgot to mention ruthless did i
yes never
forget ruthless
[Music]
you shall forget it again
help somebody help me
for the love god somebody help
[Music]
duke edward he seems to have suffered a
ruthless accident
[Music]
and now my little darling are you ready
to come to mama
[Music]
oh
this washing doesn't smell right what
would you like the dirty washing to
smell like mother
like the old mixture you made you know
it had lavender and eucalyptus and queen
spain
and all the customers said it made their
washing smell nice and fresh
she's right you know belle that's why i
bring my washing here because of all the
wonderful scents you put in
well i'm sorry we're all out of that
mixture dr thorne but uh i'm making a
new one today you want to smell
ah belle always the experimenter well it
was watching you
mixing medicines growing up that made me
think it was such a wonderful thing
well it is bill i mean there's nothing
more satisfying than seeing someone
who's sick and knowing you have what
they need
to bring them back to hell and where did
you get those from
from the forest like all the others
essence of oak
oil of pine camphor leaf i
can for and pie i i have a feeling
they may not go well together anyway you
spend far too much time wandering around
the forest
it's a dangerous place come on mom the
forest is wonderful and beautiful and i
love it
and in all your explorations you've
never seen any sign of the
famous beast the beast oh that's just a
story that people make up to scare
themselves
oh i guess this one could use some work
i knew there was something about that
combination if that had happened in my
washing boiler mother it's all trial and
error besides
i'll go out and get some herbs for a new
combination you're not going out now
why not there's no time like the present
besides
dr thorne doesn't want his washing
smelling bad does he
by all the hearts of darkness that seep
beneath this
fated earth i command you to come
forward
yes
[Music]
yes you shall do
hmm
[Music]
[Applause]
ah
[Music]
who are you
i said who are you
so
[Applause]
what are the horses yes sir
so counts concerning the throne
do you think it will come to a fight
let me put you this way i want you to
start recruiting more men
i can't bring the nobles around with
persuasion
it may take a show for us
lady helen what do we owe the pleasure
i've come here to help you become
king cousin shall we
step aside
[Music]
i was impressed with how decisively you
dealt with duke edward rudolph
duke edward's death was nothing more
than an unfortunate accident
come on i have ways of seeing these
things you know that
that's right i forgot you're doubling
witchcraft
witchcraft that can help you reach the
throne
and why would you do that what could
possibly be in it for you the fact that
i would also like to be on the throne
as your queen
excuse me am i not
beautiful your house is black as hell
and everyone knows it
if you want to be king rudolph you'll
need my black heart
[Music]
i'll get the throne without your help my
lady
good day oh no you won't because
i have at my disposal something that
will destroy any hope you have
and what exactly would that be
think about my offer rudolph
think about the pleasure i can give you
and the power and what i might do
lady helen lady helen
lady helen count are you all right of
course i am
take more than a witch to scare me
well
my pretty maiden what's your story
the beast tried to kill me the beast is
nothing more than a legend
you let your imagination run away with
you young lady do i look like an idiot
the beast killed a wolf right in front
of my eyes with a crossbow and then he
tried to kill
me crossbow that's the weapon that the
beast is supposed to use
well certainly be another feather in my
cap if i was the one to capture it
show the beast said to the people that
gotta make you king the people will
adore you for your bravery
which way to this beast
back there in the woods a little vague
no matter you're taking us
spread out look at the traps move along
spread out man run away captain there's
no need to hold me so
tight count i'm quite comfortable on
horseback but i like holding a tight
belt
besides how often does a washerwoman's
daughter get the chance to be intimate
with a lord
hmm you should feel flattered problem is
i don't so get your lecherous hands off
me
you need a lesson in manners wench and
you need a lesson in common courtesy
little trollope
[Applause]
[Music]
there's a beast after it with you later
the village
[Music]
so
what's going on elizabeth
the doctor's house that's the piece of
the roof your head is trapped
[Music]
three up there
this he's gone through the window sir
get the people out
nobody going after the beast
what happened you look until you've seen
a ghost
they're gonna kill him oh nice
isn't that a good thing he never did
anybody any harm
otto i saw him tear a man's head right
from his body
i saw it i saw the body
how do you know this was responsible
of all that's holy brought it to our
village
i promise each and every one of you here
and now i will see justice delivered
i count rudolph of breslau will destroy
that beast
i know what's the matter i have to you
have to what
talk to him who i have to someone
help me help me get him home
and so they went off after the beast
at the very minute when i could do
nothing to stop them
i've been afraid of something like this
for years
and now it had come i was helpless
and without me i knew the beast was
doomed
you must rest
he needs me he he needs me
what are you talking about that thing
just killed dr
thorne
you know you don't understand
please sheriff get some rest
[Music]
what's going on
hmm
[Music]
your eyes open
me
come on
[Music]
what's up
uh
ugh
[Music]
is anybody here
let's kill the dog
[Music]
i
oh
yes otto
he's he's very sick he couldn't come
but he's worried about you
he used to bring me food
when i was small
it was you who saved me from the wolf
wasn't it
with the crossbow
yes
and then you turned and fired your
crossbow at me why would you do that
to make you go away
i did not want you to see me
why did you kill those people tear them
to pieces what people
i have killed no people
someone killed them i saw dr thorne torn
apart i
killed you eat only
to eat ask otto
otto said you didn't kill them but he's
sick
he's very ill that's why i came
[Music]
[Applause]
you've brought hunters to kill me how
are you stay here
don't move
ah
ugh
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
god no
i had nothing to do with this it was a
creature
a troll a troll does this
look like my work does it
i am a hunter with a crossbar
i don't have a stack of blind on me
i did not bring those men here i believe
and trust you
i wouldn't trust that ambitious rat
rudolph though
as far as i'm concerned count rudolph
can rot in hell
[Applause]
so who are you what's your name
beast no that's just what they call you
what's your real name
drink this you must have a name
if i have i don't know what it is
well someone must know perhaps you're a
photo
did he bring you here i don't know all i
know is he
used to come here when i was small he
taught me to hunt
he was he was good to me
did he give you this
i don't know i don't think so
i think i've always had that since i was
a baby
what is this pattern around the rim
my pattern
[Music]
you're very clever i have a lot of time
on my hands in the winter
when the wind howls and the snow falls
[Music]
don't call yourself that
pour it
get out
i hope that was for me
but perhaps we could share it
[Music]
as a kind of loving
cup a pledge
of our future partnership
the hell are you doing here i've come to
soothe you
i understand you've had a very trying
afternoon
what the hell could you know about my
day
everything cousin you see that monster
was my creation
the beast oh it wasn't the beast that
killed the doctor or your men
and what was it it was my troll
a vicious maniacal killing machine
controlled only by me
with a little help from this
a troll yes and unless you pledge your
trough to me dear rudolph
that troll will ensure you never get
anywhere near the throne of our beloved
country
so what are you going to do now
do well you can't stay here anymore
they'll just send more men to kill you
do you have somewhere else you can hide
[Applause]
i have a shelter up between the hills
yes stay there hidden until i come back
you'll never come back of course i will
why what do you mean why
you don't have to pretend you want to
see me again
you have had some horrible things happen
to you
i guess i feel like some of it's my
fault
so count what will it be
are we partners or not say where to
entertain the idea and you call off your
troll
how does that help me get the throne
i'll help you catch the beast
the beast is famous if you were to bring
him down the whole kingdom would look up
to you
and you and i would ascend the throne
town in the world can i possibly trust
you that's simple
i need you they will not
allow a woman to rule alone
but with you by my side anything is
possible
and without me you don't stand a chance
here's to a great partnership a drink to
success my lady
i haven't decided on the partnership yet
my lord no sorry to disturb you count
told us to bring any news as soon as it
came we found this one coming out
first well well well if it is my little
spitfire
wash a woman's daughter right i believe
you and i have a little uh
unfinished business you know this woman
can
she's the one who alerted us to the
beast's rampage
then had objections when i took her with
me to go find it
what i objected to was you fondling me
like some lecherous old goat
well is that what you think of him
let me look at you hmm
i can see why count rudolph got so
excited
you're quite a beauty aren't you and you
saw the beast
i said did you see the beast
i have nothing to say to you how dare
you speak to your superiors like that
you trump
what did you see i believe the uh
rack may loosen her tongue my lady
oh no there's no need for that count
i have much better methods
[Applause]
oh yes
is that possible what is it
i thought it was dead i thought one was
dead in the monster
what is this
it's just a hammer lady
but it's not one of hers i'm done with
her now
when i haven't chad take her to the
dungeon
secure her i'll be down later all right
you
come along
she's still under sir she'll come around
soon enough
and then when she hadn't take her away
that beast must be killed can you speak
the obvious one lady no there is another
reason
it could be that the animal known as the
beast stands between us and the throne
what's the problem counts order sir to
the dungeon
chain of properly
look at this sir she's wearing ferris
[ __ ]
away with the fears you're away with the
fear of your bull run
it's not where the [ __ ] locked get an
axeman
what the hell
[Music]
i'm gonna break your damn neck
what's that noise
where the devil is everyone forget about
them we need to talk about the beast so
you keep saying
so why don't you tell me how does this
beast stand between me and the throne
stairs stairs do you remember the
stories
about maximilian's only son it was
deformed wasn't it that that died of
birth
well that's what we thought that's what
i believed until tonight
and now and now i believe
he may not have died that the beast may
actually be
maximilian's son
clear nothing here sir
[Music]
oh who else knows this
nobody i hope then why does it matter
because if somebody finds out then what
the shutters are fastened
there's no way down there sir it's
impossible give me a torch
all right listen having that monster
alive is like having a sword hanging
over our heads
and no one in that right mind is going
to accept that beast of the throne stop
arguing and understand this the beast
must die
and he must die as soon as possible
agreed the problem is going to be
finding him
there she is
[Music]
it might just be that the beautiful bell
has given us what we need to find him
the hair of the beast by thorn
and by root by blade and by
chalices
[Music]
a friend a friend that wants to warn you
where are you show yourself
the troll trap he will be there by
morning
only you can save him
[Music]
it's up to you beast go to her house in
the village
safely
i can't see you i don't know who you are
why should i believe you don't believe
me if you choose
but then my friend the troll will tear
her apart
and it will be your fault
well i think we got him hooked
impressive now
all you have to do is make sure you're
there
[Music]
through this way yes sir
that business about the troll is that
true it will be
because i have seen this creature and
it's dangerous
well now that you and i are partners
count
you're in no danger that troll is under
my command
you're absolutely sure of that oh yes
remember he will do anything for a drop
of this
and of course he wouldn't hurt anyone
i didn't want her
and there's no need for you to come with
me tomorrow morning there is every need
the beast must not be allowed to say a
word before he is killed
you're absolutely sure i'd be in that
house tomorrow morning
well if he's not we have to make sure he
is
it must look like he did the killings
and don't worry my creation
has his instructions
[Music]
we just followed the stream before she
came out
[Music]
[Applause]
try to keep
[Music]
across here that way
um
where does the washerwoman live
over there thank you
[Music]
so
um
who is it
[Music]
move back
is it time it is time
spread out surround the house let no one
pass
the first person bring me the head of
the beast was a thousand florence
listen the troll is coming through the
rules
or you're going to die
[Applause]
wow
[Music]
wait give it time to kill her
okay now
[Music]
uh
this is the part i enjoy
pierce the beast who's meant his match
matters rampage is finished
and the people of our beloved country
[Music]
congratulations count people owe you a
debt of gratitude you say the
congratulations when the job's finished
of course as soon as the trial is over
we'll be singing your praises
trial put these on him of course i don't
what trial we caught the beast
red-handed
he certainly looks guilty your honor
with the poor laundress lying dead
but king maximilian's law insists we try
people
king maximilian
before executing them and i know you're
sworn to uphold those laws
just like the rest of us while the
king's alive
so if you'll excuse me your honor
god rudolf has subdued the beast
trial will take place tomorrow
come to the window my lord and accept
the acclamation of the people
we'll take it from here the jail's very
strong
thank you thank you come on come on you
know what i'm escaping do you come on
you've a glorious fool
why didn't you kill him when you had the
chance
get him inside the jail before they turn
on him
get him locked up and bring me the key
get back all of you
move him what what's going on here sorry
belle what are you sorry about something
sir
sorry bell appears the beast has killed
your mother
it was only my regard for the law to
stop me from killing it on the spot
[Music]
the trial must be swift and just
this beast must not be allowed to commit
an atrocity like this again
jury was sworn in as soon as possible my
lord and in the meantime
our grateful thanks
[Music]
till tomorrow then
you fool you should have killed him when
you had the chance
she worked so hard
she worked so hard for me
[Music]
i could never tell her how much i loved
her
oh i think she knew i could never
tell her
who's there
try that again and i'll throw this right
between your eyes before you have time
to pull the trigger
just try it
we'll never forget your mother either of
us
but it's my fault your fault oh
[Music]
i met the beast i trusted him
if it wasn't for me he would never have
come here
you don't think you don't think the
beast killed your mother do you
otto the beast was found beside my
mother's body
it was a trial bell it was a troll he
told me
that's what he said yeah back at the
village it was a troll i mean
where is this troll anytime he comes
around something bad happens and he is a
monster
no no no no
what's really going on here otto
is this beast well it all started when
maximilian fell in love with lady helen
of augsburg
for a long time she was the only woman
faring he couldn't take his eyes off her
they went everywhere together i thought
they never married
well people say he discovered she was
cruel-hearted
and a saucer he shunned her and
how they became bitter enemies
king king married the
beautiful elizabeth of austria
and eventually they had a child
but i thought the king was childless i
thought the queen died giving a
stillborn
no no helen cast a spell on the baby and
it was born
terribly deformed poor maximilian was
distraught at the death of his wife and
he couldn't accept the child how do you
know all this otto
i was a servant in the palace and i was
ordered to
dispose of the child though he was
hideous
i couldn't bring myself to do it i took
him to an old hunting lodge
deep in the forest that i went to with
my father as a boy
i'd bring the lad food as often as i
could but eventually he didn't need it
i taught him to hunt for himself does
the king know he still has a son
no no no one does as i got to know him i
i realized that beneath that horrible
exterior was one of the kindest
gentlest beings i have ever known a true
prince bell huh
i promise you that
a true prince does he know
it would have been too cruel it sounds
like you really care for him
as if as if he were my own son
and i know he could never do any of the
things he's been accused of
i believe you it's it's just
what i think i care for him too
come on let's go see him
who goes there it's me sheriff otto
let us through holt
what's she doing here she has the right
to confront the killer of her own mother
doesn't she
now let us pass well i warn you it's got
a weapon
could kill you without even leaving his
cell how did that happen
never mind yeah well we'll take our
chances
there's no need for the rest of you to
stay here the whole night
but you're secure enough whether he's
got a weapon
or not counts orders we stay here until
the things
executed waste of time putting on trial
if you ask me
i should not kill her i know
i believe you otto told me your real
story
what real story about who you are
i think you should know the truth well
no all right then
you're probably right damn her eyes
why didn't that fool rudolph get rid of
him when he could
and why didn't i get rid of her
i'd send you in my little one but we
can't risk letting anyone
see you now can we not until the beast
been proven guilty but after that
there'll be plenty to do
so you shouldn't be in this jail cell
you should be in the royal palace
acclaimed as the next king
it's true don't you believe it
i believe you i believe otto
but who else will believe if helen used
sorcery
if she cast a spell
perhaps it could be broken
broken well in the stores there's
usually something
what
here closer
put your face between the bars
what are you doing
close your eyes
[Music]
you kissed me
i was trying to break the spell
not so easy i think
no all right that'll do
time for you to go you need to get
beauty sleep
[Applause]
the king is
the kings
[Music]
[Applause]
is
what the hell do you think you're doing
following orders
this is a trial not a torture chamber
prisoner has to be kept secure for the
safety of the jury
and also oh i am the sheriff here
and i will not let you do that on
account of you we're doing it
what the beast attacked you what are you
talking
about a car that didn't attack me oh yes
he did
[Music]
vicious huh dump him somewhere
the time he wakes up and be all over you
no sir what house is empty we've been
around the whole village
so she's escaped sir you're an idiot
never mind we've got the place around it
she tries to get him we'll have her then
perhaps he's dead
no matter what
and he woke me up and said where's the
washer woman's house
and i showed him and then he slammed my
head against the table
the washer woman was torn to pieces and
the beast was standing over her
covered in blood same monster i saw
coming out of the old hunting lodge
and there he tore men apart in minutes
well i believe that's enough from
prosecution
is there anyone here to stand up for the
accused
anyone sheriff otto
the sheriff otto here to stand up for
the accused uh sheriff
was too ill to attend my lord it seems
the beast attacked him as well
and the beast himself has nothing to say
members of the jury have you reached a
verdict
is the beast guilty or not guilty of the
death
of the washer woman anna
we have my lord what say you
guilty or not guilty guilty
my lord
[Applause]
and i hereby announce sentencing
death by beheading
immediately
[Music]
that's the axe fall
i think it's time to go
keep your hands apart
[Music]
no
this time it's the beast
i know i know he's stronger than you and
almost as ugly
but would you like some of this
well you'll
do you know what this is true
this turns living beings
into stone
and here is the perfect way of providing
the beast
with the required dose now that the
mixture is on the dagger
all you have to do is stick it in
not too afraid of him to do that how are
you
good now go into the forest
and hunt him down oh and troll
is the girl and you're in the mood
feel free to rip her head off
you came back from me of course i did
why i guess i thought it was the right
thing to do
they could have killed you it was still
the right thing to do
and also yes because i care about you
[Music]
we need to search for ardor i know but
that's not the first thing
why we have to get to the heart of this
where it all began
who it began with
the sorceress exactly
[Music]
i'm afraid what
i'm ashamed to say it but i still feared
her name
you should be angry furious
she destroyed your life
anger yours i feel
anger but she made me as i am
i fear what her magic could do me
so you have to destroy her can't she be
destroyed
i don't know but if she isn't then she
and count rudolph will have this country
in the palm of their hand
what does that matter to me you think
the people would take me as their king
no probably not
and why should i do it because it's the
right thing to do
and because i hope that you care for
this land and the people in it
the people who shine me
the people who spattered me
the people who wanted to kill me yes
those people the frightened people the
ignorant people
and also the good people people like
otto people like my mother
they need someone to stand up for them
against the sorcerer against the
sorceress
you ask a lot bill and you have a lot
[Music]
are you all right
yes yes he didn't touch me but i've
decided something
yes
[Music]
the wish must die
you look like a real hunter witch hunter
a monster hunter i'm
sorry i wasn't thinking but a troll is a
monster and and you aren't
i just look like one not to me
and besides what makes a monster is
their souls not their hides
so you and i are real monster hunters
you're not thinking of coming with me if
we go hunting my friend
we go together
[Music]
what you jibbering
stupid fool i gave you the most powerful
magic i possess
i gave you the best dagger ever made and
you
failed i ought to put you in the culture
from which you came
get in the cage you
haven't earned it so you don't get it
[Applause]
no more until i say so and should
something happen to me
no one in the world knows how to make
money
you'll be back sooner or later you'll do
anything for a drop of that
now for that damn beast
[Music]
smoke
welcome to the killing zone beast
i call on azure mazda
god of the storm
[Music]
perhaps literally
wait till this hits you
[Music]
uh
you've come here to kill me i suppose no
one deserves to die
more than you do i'm sure you're right
but consider one thing before you shoot
what's that
i made you what you are which is just
one reason why
you should die and the whole reason why
i should live
because only i know how to turn you back
if you kill me
you will stay at peace forever spare me
and i'll turn you back into the prince
you really are
now isn't that a wonderful bargain
you're
evil quite true but
you see this these came from your head
when you were still
human i use them against you and i also
use them to give life to my troll
your life and only i can take it from
him
and give it back to you all are you
you need me beast this country
needs me with my power
and your strength we could rule it
together
surely you can do it change me back into
what i am
all in good time dear boy no
you can't threaten me not if you want my
help
max axe
well that's what your father would have
called you after himself maximilian the
14th
before he felt obliged to abandon you
i'm sorry i don't respond well to
threats in fact
i hate them
nobody tells helena osborne what to do
[Music]
what a perfect morning this has become i
get to kill the beast
and slit the throat of his beloved all
in one morning
you killed her from her there was no
trust
you could have let me die you could have
forced her to
change your back if you were dead
i would have no reason to go on
do you really mean that
oh my dad
[Music]
oh god
oh there must be something here that can
help you
[Music]
ugh
he's taking over
what count rudolph
he's got the troll he's gonna make
himself the new king
what is that to do with me
everything you're the rightful heir
i would have been if i hadn't killed the
witch
you still are no matter what you look
like
if count rudolph takes over with that
monster by his side
this place could turn to hell bill
everybody hates me
and there's only two of us
three of us don't forget me otto
you came well doesn't look like you
needed me
there must be something useful we could
take from here
[Music]
huh
[Applause]
that's enough quiet all of you listen to
me
and why should we listen to you rudolph
because we have to select a new king
we have to listen to each other to you
you me
it's an excellent start after all it was
i that caught the famous beast to the
forest
oh and let it escape again that's not
fair
witchcraft was involved ah witchcraft
and aren't you surprisingly friendly
with that famous witch helen of augsburg
we're not having a witch friend for a
king so pipe down rudolph and get down
from there
yes it's true i'm friends with lady
helen of vogsberg
in fact she gave me a gift a wonderful
gift
well take it home and play with it ruby
no it'd be much more generous of me to
let it play with you
you see there's a time this creature
only answered to lady helen
but now it's transferred its affections
to me
[Music]
then have some more of we won't be this
by some goblin we're all harmed my
little red friend isn't afraid of your
horse
[Music]
how about a small round of applause
nothing duke henry
you wouldn't want to hurt my creature's
feelings would you
[Applause]
back in your cage
gentlemen nobles
it's time for us to choose a new king
[Music]
excellent work
aware there are a few of us equally
qualified by rank and by blood
for the title of king but
in view of my recent contributions to
the country's safety i'd like to put my
name forward first
i'm gonna ask each and every one of you
one by one if you'll support my becoming
the next king
starting with you duke henry do i have
your support
yes cousin rudolph i'm sorry i can't
hear you
yes cousin rudolph
the rest of you do i have your support
yes yes yes count
of course yes yes
well i'm honored and surprised by this
very unexpected nomination
i accept begging your pardon counts
sheriff honors capture the beast and the
girl
read here
so we may kneel before a new king shows
he may administer his justice
well done your majesty well done for
bringing such a monster to justice
well somebody had to do it and it had to
be you didn't it
because you were determined to condemn
me for the crimes committed by that
monster there
[Music]
i don't know what you're talking about
somebody take him away
somebody see him it
[Music]
it appears as if the council has been
using the witches spawn
to intimidate you but the truth is
there's no need for any king choosing at
all
you see before you the rightful heir to
the throne
how can that be possible are you mad
beast
no i am maximilian the 14th
son of maximilian 13 transformed at
birth into a monster
by the sorceress helen of osberg left to
die in the forest
and rescued by this man who many of you
will recognize
as once having worked as a groom in this
palace
it's the truth your honors this is the
child the good queen died giving birth
to
[Music]
and this is the royal cup that was sent
away with me
[Music]
[Applause]
who in the world do you think is gonna
believe such a foolish story
anyone with an eye for the truth rudolph
anyone who knows she was the cruel
grasping
lucifer that you are
someone like me for example
you forget the troll my friend the troll
is afraid of me rudolph almost as much
as you are
you see it was my humanity the sorceress
used to give life to that thing
and he knows i'm determined to get back
believe her you won't harm her
but only if you renounce any claim you
have to the throne
[Music]
all you have to do is say this story's a
lie
leave this land and never return
say it say it and the troll lets her go
[Music]
you ask
i hereby renounce
i hereby renounce all claim the hell you
do
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
i proclaim the start of the reign of
your new monarch
maximum to 14.
and promise to rule in the name of
for the good of every man woman and
child
in this land
[Applause]
he did exactly what he promised as long
as that couple ruled
there was peace there was prosperity
and there was also two very unusual
statues
just to remind people how lucky they
[Music]
were
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
you