wow yes marlon i know i see it it's
beautiful
oh yeah a fish can breathe out here
they did every single one of them
you did good
desirable with the great schools and the
amazing view and all that but do we
really need little heads out and they
see a whale passing right by their
bedroom
look
they're dreaming
and this half coral jr okay we're done i
like nemo
yeah
what if they don't like
what
you remember
there he is cuties here
[Music]
nemo thank you so much you can't tell
because fluid is rushing to the area now
any rushing fluids three that's all i
have oh you're okay how's the lucky fan
five or six years dad it's time for
school uh-uh-uh-uh forgot where
all right we're excited first day of
school first we check to see that the
coast is clear we go out and back in
all right come on boys
how old are sea turtles sea turtles
i don't know
i'll ask them after i'm done talking to
the shark okay
hey that snail was about to charge
[Applause]
come on we'll try over there i know
marty right marlon wow dad phil hey
you're a club clown fish are no funnier
than any other fish ah come on cloudy
up he swims up well actually the
mollusk isn't moving he's also forget
that
get out of mr johansson's yard now it
would feel better if you go play over on
the sponge beds
he looks funny ow hey what do i do
and all my other tentacles but you can't
really tell especially the zones the
zones the zones let's name the zones of
the arrests are too deep for you and me
to see
huh
all knowledge exploring is also lyrical
when you think thoughts that are in
science question okay you live in what
kind of home
i find if he's having trouble swimming
let him take a break ten feet we keep
our super esophageal ganglion to
ourselves
[Music]
you know for a clownfish he really isn't
that funny
[Music]
oh look at me i'm gonna go touch the box
come on nemo how far can you go oh i was
here if i hadn't shown up i don't know
he wasn't gonna go yeah he was too
afraid hey no it's not okay you
shouldn't be anywhere near here okay i
was right but you just can't nemo
i am a scientist sir is there any
problem you know i'm sorry i didn't mean
interrupting yes but you have a large
class and he can get lost you know from
sight if
what do you think you're doing get back
here now
stop think of me
don't touch the book
nemo
[Music]
no
no no nemo
nemo
no please no
[Music]
my son help me please
are you are you okay he's gone there
there no he's gone uh-huh and it passed
by not too long ago a white one
hi i'm dude no problem
[Music]
will you quit it well i'm trying to swim
here with ocean big enough for yourself
stop following me okay what are you
talking about you're showing me a minute
wait a minute what is going on you
already told me which way the boat was
going no it's not i know it's not i'm
i'm so sorry almost instantly it runs in
my family well
i mean at least i think it does
can i help you
something's wrong with you
oh
well hi
[Laughter]
nothing we're not doing anything we're
not even out great
what do you say oh i love parties that
sounds like fun matters
[Music]
let us all
step five bring a fish friend now do you
all have your friends
friend
it's all right testimonies hello my name
is bruce
amy
what then who's next
and uh well
well i don't i don't think
hello how about you mate what's your
problem me uh hello
my name is marlon i'm a clown fish um
there was this mollusk and he walks up
to the a sea
he was taken by these divers
what do these markings mean
hey that's mine
dory are you okay
oh
my god
don't pull up the wagon
my
[Music]
little
there's nothing to worry about oh he's
scared to death i'm from bob's fishmart
palace fishermen mail order even
decontaminated yet jacques we clean it
we
wow the big blue
or if i'm not around you can always talk
to my sister flow
not a live one
[Music]
what do we got root canal and by the
looks lightly
i can't see flow our section clearly a
headstrong no no k flex
k-flex
ugh the human mouth is a disgusting
gator glitten drill he's been favoring
that one hope he doesn't get surplus
super at the secondary portal term sorry
if i ever took a snap at you fish got to
swim bird's gotta eat hey who not this
here's darla she's my niece gonna be
eight this week a little secret
well mr tucker while that sets up i'm
gonna see a man
[Music]
poor tackles it was her
i can't go with that girl i have to get
get yourself in there you can get
yourself out
gil i just want to see him do it help me
[Music]
just like you gil
yeah
okay you got a name or what nemo
are you gonna eat that
[Music]
wow dusty
the mask where's the mask
hey what you doing it's gone i've lost
the mask would you drop it you dropped
it grumpy gills
when life gets you down you know swim
dorian i'm singing
sorry
dory do you see conscience
yeah yeah yeah i'm your conscience
waiting i see ya
i see a lot
i
i'm feeling
hey come back
come on back here i'm going to get you
healing's gone
[Music]
[Applause]
now where is that i don't know but who
cares
follow me
[Music]
to join
you are able to swim through
no nothing to bring a fire oh you said
you could do it
in five days so what are we gonna do
oh please not another one of your escape
plans sorry but they they just they
never only one who can get in and out of
that thing what we needed to do we'll
still have to clean the tank himself and
when he does he'll take us out of the
tank
[Music]
it's foolproof
who's fine he can do this
so shark mate
where are you going i'm going to peace
excuse me
ex excuse me i'll talk to you
okay fellas come back here please one
more again i'll tell you again i don't
get tired of it feature huh
here's
okay
you know alone uh-huh without without
archer you want me to leave well i mean
not yes yeah it's just you know either
delay fish you mean
you mean you don't oh don't cry
i like you hey yo do you guys know how i
can talk to pounce we're talking to the
lady not you hey-hey i've seen one of
those i'm a fish with a nose like a
sword
[Music]
[Laughter]
while they're doing their silly little
impressions i am miles from home cause
no fish in this entire ocean is gonna
help me well i'm helping you oh no he's
a good guy go easy on him he's lost his
son fabio sure oh hey they know sydney
you would
that direction and then you're gonna
follow that for a bit that's great
dorian did it oh please i'm just your
little help nailed him bye oh hey man
one more thing yes when you come to this
trip
hey hey wait up partner hold on
hello hello
flag going up
something's telling me we should swim
through it not up over we go come on
trust me on this trust you yes trust
it's what friend
boy i you wanted to go through the
trench i shall call him squishy and he's
a jellyfish bad squishy bad squishy
it's just about still
i live in this anemone and i'm i'm you
again let's be thankful this time it was
just a little one
boy
two in a row beat that story all right
listen to me i i have an idea again
rules rules rules you can't touch the
tentacles uh only the top
story
but at the same time i can do this just
be careful yeah careful i don't make you
cry
the question is dory are you hungry i'm
hungry yeah clownfish is the winner
we did it look at us
dory
[Music]
am i disqualified no you're doing fine
you're
you miss your dad don't you chuck
he's scared of the ocean
[Music]
my first escape landed on dental tools i
was aiming for i have lost count fish
aren't meant to be in a box kid it does
dark fate you can do it kid okay we
gotta be quick once you get it
[Music]
very carefully wedge that pebble do it
gil this isn't a good idea he'll be fine
try again
i got it i got it
don't make him go back in there
[Music]
what happened oh i saw the whole thing
dude first taking on the jellies you got
serious thrilling
so mr turtle oh dude mr turtle
australian current each
[Music]
dory dory is she all right
a little bit dory
ready
[Music]
[Applause]
jelly man offspring offspring
dude ow
curl away my soul they find their way
back to the big old blue all by
themselves
[Music]
sorry i was a little big on the details
so where are you going well just i don't
want to talk about it
this is gonna be good i can tell and my
son nemo water to this boat and when he
was out there these divers appeared and
i i tried to something
ferocious sharks he scared away the
sharks by blowing them up and the only
thing i can see down there
from this big horrible creature with
rain it means that he may
[Music]
last i heard he's heading towards the
harbour
okay i know who you're talking about
[Music]
i was so ready to get out
so ready to taste that oh
i'm sorry i couldn't get you back to
your father kid
that's a long way to pull it
action oh has he loosened the
periodontal ligament with the elevator
yet what am i talking about oh yeah he's
traveled hundreds of miles he's been
battling sharks and jellyfish and the
little clownfish from the reef it's my
dad he took on a shark that followed the
boat you were on like a maniac really
he's swimming and he's swimming he ties
this thing with a rock what does he get
for a reward he gets to battle an entire
wow
after all shark mate
this tank will get plenty dirty in that
time but we have to help it along anyway
this tank so filthy the dentist will
have to clean it
good work
get ready
that's it dude of course it is okay i
will now give you a rundown on proper
exiting technique
saying say the first thing again okay
jelly man go go go
turtles
most excellent
thank you dude crush
[Music]
oh hey crush crush i forgot how old
remember that
whoa
yep
we're gonna just swim
uh okay i'm thinking of something uh
orange and it's all righty mr smarty and
as orange and small that means we passed
it before and that means we're going in
circles and that means we're not going
now here let's see
okay no one there
uh no it's my turn i'm thinking of
something dark and mysterious it's a
fish we don't know
let's not die you want to get out of
here don't you of course i do well then
how are we gonna do that
little fella
hello
sydney yes and it's really really
important that we get dory i'm a little
fella
i don't think that
[Music]
don't worry whales don't eat clownfish
they eat krill
that's all thanks to you kid you made it
possible
jock i said
face
it's gonna be just if he's out there in
the harbor waiting for you right now
[Music]
uh
a whale you know i speak white no you're
insane you can't speak
hey
you there there
it's all right it'll be okay never let
anything happen to him
[Music]
of course we've stopped just stop trying
to speak whale you're gonna make things
look what you did
the water's going down it's it's half
empty hmm let's say it's half full stop
let's go to the back of the throat or he
wants a root beer floating being lunch
how do you know
[Music]
sydney
thank you
we can do this
the tank is clean
environment every five minutes
[Music]
no but the boat has to be here somewhere
come on dory we're going for the dock
it's a bell again
no
i didn't come this far to be breakfast
will you look at that right there sun's
barely up and already just fly off at
once
nemo
nemo hey he's that fish never stop
keep going he's crazy i got something to
tell you
okay don't make that
make me live
why because
[Music]
the toilet he's gonna get out of here
he's gonna get flushed
he's over there what's the dentist what
is that
hurry
[Music]
please lead to the ocean
busy
[Music]
i'm so sorry
hey dory
if it wasn't for you hey wait a minute
wait where are you going
no
no you can't
no one's ever stuck with me for so long
before
and if you leave forty
two
i remember it i did i'm home
i'm sorry dory
but i do
hey
[Music]
it's okay i'm looking for someone too
ah dad wait a minute is it your dad or
my dad my dad no p sherman 42 olivier
hey look out i'm sorry just trying to
get home
nemo
dory goodness
it's all right son it's gonna be okay
[Music]
[Applause]
no i am not gonna lose you again there's
i no you
[Applause]
can't everybody
keep swimming
just keep swimming
[Music]
[Applause]
nemo
it's okay
daddy's my goodness dad
i don't hate you
one
and he was
150 years they love to be a
[Music]
who's this it's you really do all the
things you say you did uh pardon me
well we'll see you next week keep up
with the program door remember son
have fun
[Music]
i love you too son adventure
it's a lifetime guarantee and it breaks
i had to clean the tank myself
[Applause]
[Music]
somewhere
waiting for me
the ships that go sailing
watching me
[Music]
we'll be
beyond the sea
[Music]
dome was stealing
so long
ceiling farewell
[Music]
no more sailing
no more
[Music]
wow yes marlon i know i see it it's
beautiful
oh yeah a fish can breathe out here
they did every single one of them
you did good
[Music]
desirable with the great schools and the
amazing view and all but do we really
need little heads out and they see a
whale passing right by their bedroom
look
they're dreaming
and this half coral jr okay we're done i
like nemo
yeah
what if they don't like
what
you remember in here
here he is cuties here
[Music]
hmm
you can't tell because fluid is rushing
to the area now any rushing fluids three
that's all i have oh you're okay how's
the lucky fan five or six years dad it's
time for school uh-uh-uh-uh forgot where
all right we're excited first day of
school first we check to see that the
coast is clear we go out and back in
all right come on boys
how old are sea turtles sea turtles
i don't know
i'll ask them after i'm done talking to
the shark okay
hey that snail was about to charge
[Music]
[Applause]
come on we'll try over there i know
marty right marlon wow dad phil hey
you're a club clown fish are no funnier
than any other fish ah come on cloudy
walk up he swims up well actually the
mollusk isn't moving he's if you forget
that
get out of mr johansson's yard now it
would feel better if you go play over on
the sponge beds
he looks funny ow hey what do i do
and all my other tentacles but you can't
really tell especially the zones the
zones the zones let's name the zones of
the arrest are too deep for you and me
to see
huh
all knowledge exploring is also lyrical
when you think thoughts that are in
science question okay you live in what
kind of home
i find if he's having trouble swimming
let him take a break ten feet we keep
our super esophageal ganglion to
ourselves
[Music]
be safe what's up the drop off they're
going to the drop-off what did you what
he was pony boy
you know for a clown fish he really
isn't that funny
[Music]
cyanobacteria gather
entire ecosystem contained
a hydrozoid
[Music]
oh look at me i'm gonna go touch the bot
no it's not okay you shouldn't be
anywhere near here okay i was right but
you just can't nemo
i am a scientist sir is there any
problem you know i'm sorry i didn't mean
interrupting yes but you have a large
class and he can get lost you know from
sight if
what do you think you're doing
get back here now
stop think of me
don't touch the book
nemo
[Music]
no
no no nemo
nemo
no please no
design my son help me please
are you okay he's gone there there no
he's gone uh-huh and it passed by not
too long ago a white one
hi i'm dude no problem
[Music]
will you quit trying to swim here what
the ocean big enough for you or
something stop following me okay what
are you talking about you're showing me
a minute wait a minute what is going on
you already told me which way the boat
was going ish no it's not i know it's
not i'm i'm so sorry
almost instantly it runs in my family
well
i mean at least i think it does
can i help you
something's wrong with you
oh
well hi
[Laughter]
nothing we're not doing anything we're
not even out great
what do you say oh i love parties that
sounds like fun matters
want one of them to pop
[Music]
already gone through the snakes and i'm
still starving we almost said that
let us all say the pledge
my friends not food except stinking
dolphins no step five bring a fish
friend now do you all have your friends
guys
friend
that's all the testimonies hello my name
is bruce hello bruce amy
what then who's next
and uh well
well i don't i don't think
hello how about you mate what's your
problem me uh hello
my name is marlon i'm a clown fish um
there was this mollusk and he walks up
to the a sea
[Music]
he was taken by these divers
what do these markings mean
hey that's mine
dory are you okay
[Music]
swim away
beauty
there's nothing to worry about oh he's
scared to death
i'm from bob's fish mart palace
fishermen mail order decontaminated yet
jacques
we're cleaning
the big blue
or if i'm not around you can always talk
to my sister flow not a live one
[Music]
what do we got root canal and by the
looks lately
i can't see flow our section clearly a
headstrong no no k flex head strokes
oh the human mouth is a disgusting gator
glidden drill he's been favoring that
one hope he doesn't get surplus super at
the secondary portal term sorry if i
ever took a snap at you fish got to swim
bird's gotta eat hey who not this here's
darla she's my niece gonna be eight this
week a little secret
well mr tucker while that sets up i'm
gonna see a man
[Music]
poor tackles he was her
i can't go with that girl
touch him
get yourself in there you can get
yourself out
gil i just want to see him do it
[Music]
just like you gil
yeah
no kid you got a name or what nemo
hmm
[Music]
wow dusty
the mask where's the mask
hey what you doing it's gone i've lost
the mask would you drop it you dropped
it grumpy gills
when life gets you down you know swim
dory no singing
sorry
dory do you conscience
yeah yeah yeah i'm your conscience
waiting i see ya
i see a lot
hi
i'm feeling
hey come back
come on back here i'm going to get you
feelings gone
the mask
[Music]
that's great keep it real
[Applause]
[Music]
surely
42 don't even don't let me see wow
[Applause]
that's great
now where is that i don't know but who
cares
i remember
nemo
follow me
[Music]
you are able to swim through
none of things bring a fire oh you said
you could do it
in five days so what are we gonna do
oh please not another one of your escape
plans sorry but they they just they
never only one who can get in and out of
that thing what we need to do we'll
still have to clean the tank himself and
when he does he'll take us out of the
tank
[Music]
it's foolproof
who's fine he can do this
so
again i don't get tired of it be sure
huh
here's
okay
you know alone uh-huh without without
what aren't you you want me to leave
well i mean not yes yeah it's just you
know either delay fish you mean
you mean you don't oh don't cry
i like you hey yo do you guys know how i
can look to pounce we're talking to the
lady not you hey well i've seen one of
those i'm a fish with a nose like a
sword
saw that what lots of legs live in the
ocean
i'm serious
while they're doing their silly little
impressions i am miles from home because
no fish in this entire ocean is gonna
help me well i'm helping you oh no he's
a good guy go easy on him he's lost his
son fabio sure do oh hey they know
sydney
you would
that direction and then you're gonna
fall out for a bit that's
you did it oh please i'm just your
little help nailed him bye oh hey man
one more thing yes when you come to this
trip
hey hey wait up partner hold on
[Music]
flag going up something's telling me we
should swim through it not over we go
come on trust me on this trust you yes
trust it's what
boy
i you wanted to go through the trench i
shall call him squishy and he's a
jellyfish bad squishy bad squishy
i live in this anemone and i'm i'm you
again let's be thankful this time it was
just a little one
you can't touch the tentacles uh only
the top
sorry
but at the same time i can do this just
be careful yeah careful i don't make you
cry with speed the question is dory are
you hungry hungry yeah clown fish is the
winner
we did
[Music]
no you're doing fine you're
you miss you're dead don't you shook
he's scared of the ocean
my first escape landed on dental tools i
was aiming for i have lost count fish
aren't meant to be in a box kid it does
dark bait you can do it kid okay we
gotta be quick once you get it
[Music]
gil this isn't a good idea you'll be
fine try again
i got it i got it
don't make him go back in there
[Music]
dude
focused you
what happened oh i saw the whole thing
dude first taking on the jellies you got
serious
thrilling so mr turtle oh dude mr turtle
australian current each
[Music]
dory dory is she all right ah a little
bit
hmm
[Applause]
[Music]
offspring offspring
they find their way back to the big old
blue all by themselves
[Music]
sorry i was a little big on the details
so where are you going well you see i
don't want to talk about it
this is going to be good i can tell and
my son nemo
water to this boat and when he was out
there these divers appeared and i i
tried to suffer
ferocious sharks he scares away the
sharks by blowing them up and the only
thing i can see down there
from this big horrible creature with
rain it means that he may be on his way
here right now that
[Music]
i heard he's heading towards the harbour
okay i know who they're talking about
[Music]
i was so ready to get out
so ready to taste that over
i'm sorry i couldn't get you back to
your father kid
that's a long way to pull it too
action who has he loosened the
periodontal ligament to the elevator yet
uh what am i talking about oh yeah he's
traveled hundreds of miles he's been
battling sharks and jellyfish and the
little clownfish from the reef it's my
dad he took on a shark that followed the
boat you were on like a maniac really
he's swimming and he's swimming he tries
to sleep
what does he get for a reward he gets to
battling in time
he was looking for you after all shark
mate
this tank will get plenty dirty in that
time but we have to help it along anyway
this tank's so filthy the dentist will
have to clean
that's it dude of course it is okay i
will now give you a rundown on proper
exiting technique
most excellent thank you dude crush
[Music]
oh hey crush crush i forgot how old
remember that
whoa
yep we're gonna just swim
uh okay i'm thinking of something uh
orange and it's all righty mr smarty
pants
orange
let's see
okay no one there
uh no it's my turn i'm thinking of
something dark and mysterious it's a
fish we don't know
let's not die you want to get out of
here don't you of course i do well then
how we gonna do that
little fella
hello
sydney yes and it's really really
important that we get dory i'm a little
fella
i don't think that
[Music]
don't worry whales don't eat clown fish
they eat krill
that's all thanks to you kid you made it
possible
jock i said
hello barbara sorry i'm like okay okay
here we go to me
don't you people realize we are oh
bye bro what did you hear that shark
bait
he's out there in the harbor waiting for
you right now
[Music]
oh
come on you gotta try this will you just
stop it
whale you know i speak weight no you're
insane you can't speak those armor
hey
you there there
it's all right it'll be okay never let
anything happen to him
and of course we've stopped just stop
trying to speak whale you're gonna make
things look what you did
the water's going down
it's half empty hmm let's say it's half
full stop it let's go to the back of the
throat or he wants a root beer floating
being lunch okay he stopped talking
how do you know
[Music]
thank you
we can do this
[Music]
the tank is clean
hey peach
your tank environment every five minutes
ph balance
[Music]
that would have been enough
no but the boat has to be here somewhere
come on dory we're going for the duck
it's a bell again
no
i didn't come this far to be breakfast
sun's barely up and already just fly off
at once
nemo
nemo hey he's that fish you know stop
okay don't make that
make me live
why because
[Music]
he's gonna get out of here he's gonna
get worse he's dead
he's over there what's the dentist what
is that
[Applause]
[Music]
all the
please lead to the ocean
[Music]
i'm so sorry
hey dory
if it wasn't for you hey wait a minute
wait where are you going
no
no you can't
no one's ever stuck with me for so long
before
and if you leave forty
two
i remember it i did i'm home
i'm sorry dory
but i do
hey
[Music]
um
excuse me
remember it's okay
i'm looking for someone too
[Music]
ah dad wait a minute is it your dad or
my dad
no p sherman 42
and then
here you are i found you you're not dead
and your father
have you seen an orange fish swim by and
it looks just like him
mine
oh hey look out i'm sorry just trying to
get home
nemo
dory goodness
it's all right son it's gonna be okay
[Music]
i know you can can't
[Applause]
everybody
[Music]
just keep swimming
[Applause]
nemo
it's okay
thank goodness
[Music]
sandy plankton
i'm aboard
well hello nemo who's this exchange did
you really do all the things you say you
did uh pardon me
well we'll see you next week keep up
with the program dory remember son
have fun
[Music]
i love you too son adventure
the lifetime guarantee and it breaks i
had to clean the tank myself
[Applause]
[Music]
somewhere
waiting for me
the ships that go sailing
watching on me
[Music]
beyond the sea
ceiling
[Music]
so long
feeling farewell
no more sailing
[Music]
no more
so
[Music]
do
[Applause]
[Music]
do
you
[Music]
[Applause]
uh
[Music]