who is it
it's me dolly come in
[Music]
good evening mr peabody
hello dolly
hello my name is jack
jack stark i'm a detective
i'm a private detective i'm 45 years old
i'm divorced
this is my office 2244 laguna street
san francisco california
the usa today
is friday
good morning jack good morning nadine
how are you today
i'm okay well not really
i'm tired and i'm bored
and you i'm fine thanks good
then make some coffee where is it
here it is
this is nadine she's my secretary
my personal secretary she's
28 and she's not married
she is single oh hello
nice to meet you
answer the phone nadine
[Music]
hello hello is this golden gate garage
no it isn't is this 285 4790
no i'm sorry wrong number
who is it i don't know wrong number
[Music]
wrong number this is not
my day
come in
[Music]
how do you do my name is mrs peabody
are you jack stark yes i am and this
is my secretary nadine how do you do
nice to meet you can i help you
i hope so it's about
my husband sit down mrs peabody
nadine get a chair please
would you like a cup of coffee tea
please
of course nadine
make some tea please
now what's his name then who
your husband patrick his name's patrick
and what's his last name peabody
of course what's your
first name priscilla
oh that's a nice name thank you your
first name is priscilla
and your last name is peabody
how do you spell that please what
your last name how do you spell your
last
name oh my surname
p-e-a-b-o-d-y
nadine take some notes
where are you from mrs peabody you have
a funny accent
i'm from england i'm english
is your husband english no
he isn't he's american
oh excuse me bt is ready here
take this get me the typewriter nadine
let's see mrs peabody you're english
you're married and your husband
is american you are an excellent
detective mr stark
thank you mrs peabody
[Music]
here it is thanks
well mrs peabody some standard questions
what's your address where do you live
my address is 3751
sunrise lane san francisco
[Music]
what's your phone number two
three seven six four five
nine
[Music]
how old are you what's your age
i'm sorry now what's
your occupation what do you do
are you a housewife no i'm not
i'm a fashion designer i see
[Music]
now what does your husband do
what's his occupation he
is a photographer
[Music]
first name priscilla
last name peabody
marital status married
address 3751
sunrise lane san francisco
phone number two three
seven six four
five nine occupation
fashion designer age
husband's name patrick
husband's occupation photographer
would you like some cookies cookies oh
biscuits no thank you cream
no thank you sugar yes please
i'm sorry well don't just stand there
clean it up
shop at dicey's department stores where
women's
fashion is our passion
now practice
how do you do
nice to meet you
good morning
how are you
i'm okay and you
i'm fine thanks
[Music]
and here are the two tones
mrs peabody i don't like
divorce cases this isn't a divorce
case mr stark i love my husband
and he loves me then
why don't you go to the police i'm a
famous designer
a fashion designer i don't want the
publicity
okay don't worry now tell me about your
husband's routine
what does he do every day well
he usually gets up at eight o'clock in
the morning
that's early he always has breakfast
and reads the newspaper then what does
he do
well he leaves home at 9am
he arrives at his studio at half past
nine he usually works in his studio
until six o'clock
but he never arrives late for dinner do
you
always have dinner together yes we do
mr stark i'm worried
where is he
[Music]
we have his camera his wallet
his keys and some photographs
yeah but these photos aren't right
there's no picture of me in there
i know be quiet
hello far east import export
this is mr dicey do you have the picture
no i don't but i think his wife has it
well get it i want the photograph
and the negative you have an hour slouch
yes mr dicey don't worry be happy
meet me here in an hour
he wants the photograph and the negative
in and out
now these are the peabody's keys what's
their address
3751 sunrise lane
classy barrio let's go
now one more thing mrs peabody can you
describe your husband
he's handsome of course of course
he isn't tall and he isn't short
average height yes he's average height
he's got brown hair and big brown eyes
hmm cute
do you have a picture of him no but i
have his pictures
what do you mean these are photos of my
last fashion show
patrick sometimes takes pictures at my
fashion shows
interesting and this is his card
peabody's photo studio now
excuse me mr stark it's late don't worry
mrs peabody
i'll find him goodbye mr stark goodbye
nadine i have a job for you
i know type these notes
no not that follow mrs peabody
really that's right some rail detective
work
okay thanks jack
see you later
[Music]
now practice
hi i'm dolly i'm a model
i'm young i'm thin
i'm beautiful i have blue eyes
how do you do my name is mr dicey
i am the director of dicey's department
stores
i'm rich i'm famous and i'm happy
i get up at nine o'clock i take a shower
then i eat breakfast
i wake up at 10 o'clock
i have breakfast in bed i read the
newspaper
now tell me about your husband's routine
what does he do every day well
he gets up at eight o'clock in the
morning that's early
he always has breakfast and reads the
newspaper
then what does he do well
he leaves home at nine am he
arrives at his studio at half past nine
he usually works in his studio until six
o'clock
now one more thing mrs peabody can you
describe your husband he's handsome
of course of course
he isn't tall and he isn't short
average height yes he's average height
he's got brown hair and big brown
eyes cute
[Music]
wow this is a beautiful
house there are four bedrooms
and two bathrooms there's an
enormous kitchen and a large dining room
what are you doing i'm looking for a
photograph
remember ah
i don't think it's here
hello
now what are you doing
i'm writing a note to mrs peabody
let's go
hello hello jack this is nadine
i'm in front of the peabody's house
where's mrs peabody she's buying some
flowers
now she's walking up her front steps
she's opening the front door
she's going into her house good work
what are you doing i'm looking at mr
peabody's photographs
there are lots of beautiful models in
elegant dresses
working hard eh
call me later
wait a minute what's this
[Music]
feet
oh my god
what's happening mrs peabody are you all
right
no i'm not what are you doing here
are you following me yes
i am that's lucky look at this mess
what's that it's a note what does it say
urgent bring photos of fashion show
far east import export
pier 13.
what are you doing i'm calling jack
he's not in the office he's probably
having lunch
now what we can't wait for him
there's no time come on
fashion sale starts today shop at
dicey's
where women's fashion is our passion
oh my head
where am i who am i
are you all right i think i'm all right
who are you what are you doing here
i'm jack stark i'm a private detective
are you mr peabody
i don't know can you walk
i think i can walk
[Music]
where are we going i'm taking you to my
office
[Music]
now practice
what's your name dolly
are you married no i'm not
i'm single how old are you
i'm 22 years old what do you do
i'm a model
what are you doing i'm reading
dolly
no i'm not i'm single
i'm 22 years old
i'm a model
i'm reading
eyes
ears
nose
mouth
face
head
arms
hands
clap your hands
touch your nose
touch your ears
close your eyes
wow is a beautiful house
there are four bedrooms and two
bathrooms
there's an enormous kitchen and a large
dining room what are you doing
i'm looking for a photograph remember
i'm looking at mr peabody's photographs
there are
lots of beautiful models in elegant
dresses
[Music]
this is pier 13 and that's
far east import export i can see that
you wait here
dolly what are you doing here
i can't tell you mrs peabody
do you have the photos no i don't who
has them
a private detective has them private
detectives
that's right jack stark chuck stark
well you can call him then
ten and nine
nineteen it's a sunny day today
listen mr stark this is mrs peabody
do you have that role of film yes i do
it's your wife my wife
take it to the golden gate bridge meet
me there at one o'clock
it's urgent
[Music]
can you do that no problem i have a
surprise for you mrs peabody and i have
one for you
[Music]
goodbye
can't we finish the game
[Music]
21 i win come with me
where are we going i want to introduce
you to your
wife
can you see something interesting who
are you
i ask the questions come on
inside
[Music]
nadine
stop her
i can stop her
[Music]
now you can relax
give me the knife
[Music]
lovely view you can see the golden gate
bridge from here
i know you you're mr dicey of dicey's
department stores
that's right mrs peabody women's fashion
is our passion
now i want that photograph
give it to me i don't have it
jack stark has it and he's waiting for
me on the golden gate bridge right now
[Music]
and he can't save you yes i can
now
[Music]
thank you mr stark call me
jack
[Music]
now practice
what's your name
i don't know where are you from
i don't know what's your job
i don't know do you work in an
office
i don't know are you okay
no i'm not
i don't know
lovely view you can see the golden gate
bridge from here
i know you you're mr dicey of dicey's
department stores
that's right mrs peabody women's fashion
is our passion
now i want that photograph
give it to me
now you can relax
give me the knife
[Music]
great job thanks you arrived
just in time you obviously didn't wait
on the golden gate bridge
no i didn't you telephoned me i heard
the sound of a ship
a ship's horn i looked at my watch
it was exactly 12 30.
then i looked at the newspaper i read
the schedule for ship
sailings here it is friday
october 2nd 12 30 pier 13
the pacific jewel sailing for hong kong
smart jack where were you last night
i don't know i can't remember
he was in his studio mrs peabody
okay what happened
i answered mr peabody steele
i didn't want to but slouch wanted some
photos
shut up go on he waited outside
then he came in he hit mr pewdie on the
head with this camera
we looked everywhere but we couldn't
find the right photos
why did they want the photos they didn't
want
all photos they wanted this one that's a
photo of dolly
dolly and mr dicey and slouch
can you see them what are they doing
now i remember i was at your
fashion show last night i photographed
the models
and i asked you for the roll of film do
you remember
our next model is wearing a lavender
dress
a strapless evening gown designed by the
famous fashion designer
mrs priscilla peabody
that's it finished give me the film dear
here you are see you later i have some
work at the studio
but what was the money for what do we
have
here
[Music]
those are my dresses these
are copies of your dresses mrs peabody
dolly stole your designs i didn't want
to
how much did you pay for them mr
dicey too much
mr peabody this was not their day
crime doesn't pay
now practice
slouch is wearing a black hat
a black shirt
and a gray suit
where were you last night
last night what time
where were you at eight o'clock
i was at a fashion show were you alone
no i wasn't i was with a friend who were
you with
i was with slouch
last night what time
i was at a fashion show
no i wasn't i was with a friend
i was with slouch
what happened i answered mr peabody's
studio i didn't want to
but slouch wanted some photos shut up
great job nadine thanks you arrived
just in time you obviously didn't wait
on the golden gate bridge
no i didn't you telephoned me
i heard the sound of a ship a ship's
horn
i looked at my watch it was exactly 12
30. then i looked at the newspaper
i read the schedule for ship sailings
where were you last night i don't know
i can't remember he was in his studio
mrs peabody
but what was the money for
what do we have here
those are my dresses these
are copies of your dresses mrs peabody
dolly stole your designs
you