[Music]
it's a family reunion everybody's here
gathered round the table full of holiday
cheer
put on a record nice and low
so by the window we can watch the snow
oh my
it's mighty cold outside
so call up your friends
gather your neighbors
spend time together as long
love
that's what we had
since
1885 when my family the fips built this
house
we've celebrated over 133
christmases here
that's a lot of christmases
and about the last 60 of them have been
open to other families
ever since my grandpa turned it into a
bed and breakfast
all right everybody get out your holiday
spirit and put on your boogey boots it's
time to dance
sports come on baby girl
dance with us give me just one second i
got these in the oven about to burn i
will be right back
but
[Music]
where's your sister by the way uh
sorry mister but i need to steal this
beautiful lady away for a little bit
dad it's tradition i don't make the
rules what yes you do i don't want to
dance
[Music]
what happened
did you get a fight with a baker
all right i think the flower won
well i like it or not
it's your turn
dad i i can't go out there like this i
mean i'm a mess
well i'm sorry but you know what i don't
know what i said
i know
you can't you can't break tradition
christmas
okay
[Music]
and meet somebody
all the guys i know are losers and
didn't you tell me to never date a loser
i do
but at this point
i'm brightening my horizons
[Music]
i miss mom
now
me too
that's what i want for you
for all my girls
the kind of love that never fails
promise me you won't let this place run
your life
whatever comes to stumbling block
don't hesitate let it go
this place is not
our family
we
are our family
[Music]
promise me
i promise
[Music]
lizzie lou
oh good morning sleepyhead
okay listen we have one short hour to
get our guests up
fed packed and out the door to their cat
so i just need to know
are you with me
okay
[Music]
and there it is
the shakespeare chateau
a gem of our little town
st joseph missouri
at first glance you may be mesmerized by
the house
three stories of intricate woodwork tile
floors plated ceilings maybe the ornate
dragon staircase or
many people's favorite the embedded
statue of shakespeare carved above the
fireplace
but i can assure you
after you've lived here your entire life
it becomes
one big fat drawn out
chore
one more thing dear oh you i seem to
have forgotten my toothbrush would you
happen to have an extra
i yes i can do that i will
[Music]
you're welcome
oh hey hey oh you got any bandages i'm
waiting here
hey i'm on blood platinus
[Music]
okay okay i need to chime in here my
name is grant ogden and i'm proud to say
this is my extremely handsome son levi
two cool guys with dashingly debonair
smiles
our sophisticated morning routine
usually starts with pop tarts cereal and
a very important ritual to select
today's business wardrobe
if you want to be a winner you've gotta
dress like one
well
since one sister packed up and left
in a heated rage apparently two sisters
can run a bed and breakfast things
couldn't be any more
superfluously
hectic
just one more thing i wonder if you have
another of those little to-go sized
lotion bottles you know for the plain
deer get so dry okay i won't go thank
you thank you oh there you are dear
thank you so much here you are
because you're so cute wow
a whole quarter yes it is don't spend it
all in one place don't worry i won't
my gosh yes
searching everywhere for it
i found it in the other room
now your mother
always said family heirlooms had a
strange magic
i could never figure it out
that means
it still has a part to play
may i sure
i'm proud of you
thanks dad you're welcome i gotta go
bye
[Music]
there's a comforting charm about this
town that makes you feel like mystery
and magic are just around the corner
waiting to be discovered and that at any
moment something amazing is about to
happen
do you ever feel that way
love comes along and you sing in a song
like a blue
bird
[Music]
love comes around and you finally found
an excuse
love says come here and a voice in your
ear whispers new
words
love hunts you down till you're pinned
to the ground it's no use
you know it's totally normal to have a
second job
and if you're gonna work somewhere you
might as well enjoy it
i love the people i work with and the
extra money
but i really love to read
it's a perfect fit
i'm sure some people get to pet little
puppies for a living maybe even deliver
cute babies but i've been given the
nickname the hammer because i'm required
to squash the tiny villagers that don't
appease the overlords of banking
it's part of the job
hi stacy it's actually stephanie yeah
have brenda get me those reports okay
right away yeah thank you
hey morning mr ogden hey nice suit
thanks junior banker
good morning mr ogden morning i've got
your two o'clock scheduled sounds great
thanks you're welcome
as long as i can remember
i find that people are either at their
best
or
call yourself a librarian at their worst
during the holiday season merry
christmas
hey new guy
hold up a second
what's the new security passcode
1557 backslash nacho what's the prime
interest rate
yesterday's 3.75 today
3.5
who did i take to prom
my sister
yeah i did
rudy duty fresh and fruity dougie dude
[Music]
look at you look at you look at this
yeah you approve huh yeah
now really you ready man born ready all
right be a shark wait ready
even though it may be cold outside
there's a warmth that comes with a
a good novel
it can give you the fiery hope that
one day prince charming may just
jump out of the pages and sweep you off
your feet
like a pawn in the game
i admit i like to read occasionally
when there's absolutely nothing to do
outside
why waste time on fairy tales and phony
baloney love stories
i mean really has a book ever help
somebody fall in love
has it ever showed them who they're
meant to be with
i doubt it
[Music]
love comes along for the week and the
strong you can
[Music]
you know
i read in a magazine last month about
women with pre-holiday psychosis
they get so lonely they start
hallucinating and talking to people who
aren't even there
are you suggesting that i'm
hallucinating
well
it is december
and you were just talking to yourself so
if i ever start to feel a little down i
simply just throw myself into my work
and i don't even notice oh
yeah they have a term for that it's
called post-holiday psycho no max it's
psychosis not psycho and it's pre not
post the cycle happens before the
holiday that's why we hurry up and get
our friend hooked up before the post
cycle you guys i am not a psycho
i don't need a guy to make me happy and
besides i got both of you
oh
that's good i don't have a lot of
friends
but i think that's denial
yeah
well
anyway maybe you'll change your mind
after today's reading hour we have a
special guest
a special guest
grant have you ever been scuba diving
there's this little beach i go to every
year off the cayman islands
crystal clear water
tan legs as far as the eye can see
truthfully i'm just a visitor there now
the board has offered me early
retirement
huge pension
i can buy that beach house
and sink my teeth into that
real estate
but
we need someone young
someone who can be in charge
someone to take over as vp
maybe even president
and we think
that person
could be you grant
wow
i don't know what to say
and if not i do have a nice set of tan
legs so
i'm counting on you son
i got this
i can't believe you set me up on a date
it was max's idea
aunt his friend
but
what did you think
i mean he's
kind of different
he always liked mystery and he's sort of
funny i mean for the kids obviously you
always wanted kids and he's just
coming up to the counter
oh
hey
brooke it's so good to finally meet you
finally yeah we've met an acting class
there's a lot of wannabe actors total
fakes with this guy natural super cool
a natural what
i just feel like i've now been
reborn
as a true artist
acting
painting
stretching
brook
i know this all may seem rather sudden
but i just feel like you and i are
two floating sticks
in the stream of life
and suddenly
our paths have crossed
how about dinner
well
sure
why not
i'm sorry i touched you thank you
thank you
we're gonna
go hang out he's really cool
[Music]
he's weird
but i like weird
[Music]
come my reindeer that's where we will
fly
there's christmas cheer in the land
[Applause]
well hello and what are you checking out
today snakes and froggy books they're my
favorite well you must be very brave
because i am deathly afraid of snakes
and froggies
and who's your friend that's my dad
we're apparently best pals
and i like snakes and froggies
well bravery must run in the family um
can i get your zip code please sure six
four five zero
well looks like you're all set all right
um is there anything else i can help you
with today
yeah you know what there is there's this
book i've been looking for
what is that book you know you you know
the name of the book do you remember the
name of the book no neither of us
remember the name of the book you know
what it's okay i work wednesday through
saturday so if you think of it you can
just come back and i'd be happy to help
you
okay sounds good thank you i appreciate
that until then
until then
all right
[Music]
dad
what are you doing
well i'm just trying to figure out how a
seven-year-old with no driving
experience
can outsmart a full-grown adult at a
racing gate
no that's not what i mean
okay what do you mean
i'm concerned about you dad you're
lonely
emphatic
what are you talking about
i was just talk show and they said a
full grown man over the age of 30 is
more likely to become sterile it's
sterile anyway
buddy that's why we moved here in a
smaller town
simpler life settle down you know
get out of here
fine i'll go
you know what get more life advice from
dr phil it's doing you good i'm gonna
get a snack you want anything
you know what i hate about fast coffee
what i mean you take a plastic cup
tossed in a machine
add some water push a couple buttons and
in seconds it's done
it's a cold way to make hot coffee
it's easy
that's why i like it
but there's no passion no art no love
put into it see with a barista you get a
coffee chef
an artist someone who carefully and
uniquely and beautifully weaves a flavor
into your coffee
so
perfectly unpredictable
well you my dear are always predictably
unpredictable
thank you
thank you very much but i'm sorry
rules are rules and we're gonna have to
close your business
look
sometimes life hands us lemons and
you just have to make lemon bars
oh i i can make you some lemon bars oh
okay um
miss jennings i could get in a lot of
trouble for this but here's what i'm
gonna do i'm gonna send you over to mike
at clarendon bank down the street he's
gonna work with you i'm gonna talk to
him have a postpone all your loan
repayments until your business is cash
positive okay
all right
[Music]
have a great day
you're the best
i just always thought when
fate and destiny aligned with me some
kind of
sign you know you've been watching
romance movies again haven't you
maybe
dang man you are ruthless
that's why they call you the hammer
even the sweet old ladies that's me
the sweet old lady killer
really good feeling
good feeling
[Music]
uh did you drop your book
i don't have a book
well it's
not mine
who's is this
how to make great friends and lasting
relationships a self-help romance novel
sounds like you that's a good sign right
sign
we were just talking about signs yeah
and
oh don't drag me into this is a random
occurrence
a sign huh
so now what i mean
i don't know i i can't just turn into
lost and found because i mean they'll
just borrow it away
oh
there's a name
and a number
rudy
what kind of name do you think is rudy
this rookie person might not even
realize it's missing
well
i'm gonna go unlock the library now
[Music]
who are you
hello
rudy you may be wondering
who this is
destiny has a funny way of using a lost
book and a coffee shop to
what am i doing
stupid
i need details tell me about your crazy
college days all right tell me tell me
about the the big city girls huh dude
you know what i like that i'm a
traditional guy looking for a
traditional gal
i just want to live a simple life
this is ridiculous
it's just a text
[Music]
hello rudy
you don't know me
but
i found your book in the coffee shop
with the name rudy and this number
let me know if you would like your book
back
it's just a text
let's start the second
i am not buying it i'm not buying this
white night routine
you're a shark
keep you shark and a knight all right
what was the name of that place we had
breakfast at this morning ah welcome to
the brioche home of the giant brioche
yeah yeah yeah brioche
someone found my book
i left my book at the cafe
okay is she cute
well i mean assuming it's a she there is
a book emoji on the text yeah that's
definitely a she that is a sheep for
sure yeah well hey i gotta go vlorsky's
been up by asking for it for a while i
need to get some paperwork done
hey brooke how's the look
no
two turtle doves in a christmas bush
we haven't even got to the turtle oh you
met us that's it's funny oh my gosh it's
him
and who the guy from the coffee shop
with the book
let me know when and where to meet up
i just moved back to town from when i
was a kid
not very familiar with all the new
changes thank you for rescuing my book
you must be a very kind soul
i like to think so
so he's got my number
should i tell him my name no he could be
a serial killer
happens every day
so i take it with a name like rudy you
must play football
only in middle school
rudy was a nickname i only played one
game at the end of the season i scored
the winning touchdown
never played again
old friends still call me rudy
how about you
do you have a name
sparks
[Music]
so
i have to ask
are you one of those guys that if you
were stranded on a desert island all you
would need is plenty of beer
and your dog to keep you company
more of a netflix movie guy give me a
zombie flick any day
i happen to be allergic to dogs
they're not zombies
did i mention i have an underground
bunker fully stocked
just kidding
darn for a second there i thought i was
about to drop what i was doing and marry
you instantly your turn
what do you like about christmas the
most
hot cocoa
or
opening presents
hmm
honestly
watching people open the gifts i gave
them
oh very santa claus view i like it
well
it was good meeting you over at text
you seem like someone i would enjoy
getting to know
[Music]
uh
oh
[Music]
uh welcome everyone i'm grant
and this is doug
uh yes this first one we call el palazzo
magnifico
this tuscan home has uh in-ground pool
four-car garage it's nestled in the
pride of country club and it's just a
stone's throw away from the golf course
uh this one we call
the kennedy equity 170
pool golf and it comes fully furnished
stop stop
stop
i
don't care if it's new
old as three fireplaces
a red ferrari a pair of ten legs
if i'm basically not stealing it
i don't want it
now
show me
a real
deal
um
okay uh mr
mr bilbuscus sir i
i think i have just the thing
807 let's do it yeah
807 hall street one of the victorian
gems of st joseph
we call it victorian secret
all right that's enough doug
it's a bed and breakfast called the
shakespeare chateau
priceless original stained glass windows
intricate carpentry literally from floor
to ceiling
this masterpiece is worth well over two
million five years ago the estate was
used as collateral for a relatively
small 50k fix-up loan
that note ended last month with a
remaining 30k in debt
it's beginning to look a lot like
default
they're in default yep they are and they
don't even know it which legally
entitles us to the entire two million
estate
you
conniving little devil
you soul sucking spineless banker
well done my boy
you did it you did it
so when can we wrap up this little gift
for our distinguished guest the notice
has already been sent
we foreclose on december 24th in theory
we can have you sign done in roasting
chestnuts with your girlfriend come
christmas morning
[Music]
this is pretty
mom got that for you the year you were
born
mom
we miss you
i'm gonna hang it on the front of the
tree
[Music]
hey brooke
merry christmas
katie
what are you doing here
uh
freezing at the moment you gonna
let me in or what
oh yeah
come on
hey
oh
oh my gosh you've grown so much
so speaking of
is that for me yes ma'am all the way
from seattle whoa
awesome
this christmas will be perfect with you
here which are you staying in
uh
that kind of depends
i'll make you some of my famous chai tea
sounds good
i could have just wired you the money
how much you need this time
that's not why i'm here and why are you
here
can i not come home for christmas to see
my family
ah
not here to visit
i want to stay
for how long
permanently
well that
is not gonna happen
okay
i have just as much right to this house
as you and lizzy
where were you anyway
as far away as i could get
but
brooke things change okay and i need to
be here look i don't have time for this
so uh grab your teeth stay the night and
leave in the morning
are you serious
no brooke
you need me here i'm not leaving
to quote shakespeare
nothing will come of nothing
what is that supposed to mean
it means no
[Music]
don't even start with me
um
how to box your old stuff
was gonna
throw it away but i mean it is
yours so
i think it's fine if you stay for two
weeks maybe three tops but then i think
you should notice
and
what
it says there's
whatever a balloon notice is and that we
owe 30
000 on the house
it's got to be like junk mail right
i can help
you're gonna help huh
with what
money you don't have a job you can't get
or with a business that you know
absolutely nothing about so please
enlighten me katie how are you going to
help huh
i can be here with my sisters
yeah
and we'll see how long that lasts
[Music]
here's your chai tea katie
thanks
i'm glad you're back
me too
[Music]
hello
hi i need to speak to mr ogden about a
home loan of course
buying a house with the hubby for the
kiddos
no
um he actually wants to take my house
robbing me of any opportunity of having
a hubby or some kiddos
thanks
did you have an appointment
he's like four strokes down he said
they're holding his nine iron and he
says to me if we don't close this deal
i'm gonna need another
yeah drink still got it buddy
man you can't go back there ma'am
you need an appointment
i don't know who you people think you
are running your bank like some credit
card scam mr ogden mr big fancy bank
executive well i've got news for you i
have never missed a payment and now you
want to take my house
you mr ogden are a despicable man you
make my blood boil just looking at you
what
that's miss drawing it's you
you're the dad from the library
stacy i've got this
mr gran ogden big fancy pants executive
loan officer at your service
brooke phipps
i run the shakespeare chateau
i thought you were a librarian
can we go talk in my office maybe like
adults
do i need an appointment
not today after you
[Music]
please have a seat
you know
you think you're so charming and cute
showing up to the library with your
adorable son
were you spying on me i mean is that
what you were doing
let's just focus on why you're here okay
explain to me exactly what that means
well um in 1997 mr phipps had previously
signed for a considerable loan to make
some repairs on a very costly estate
well the bank set up a balloon note
which means monthly payments would be
made until the end of the note on which
the remaining balance would be paid a
balance of 30 000 dollars
miss phipps balloon notes are very
common in this industry i'm sure mr
phipps was well aware of the contract he
was getting himself into
okay so i mean what do we do we need to
sign another loan to cover this one
unfortunately at this time there are no
loan options available
the bank is gonna have to do whatever
necessary to recoup its losses
take my house
i mean
the house is worth more than that stupid
loan miss phipps the note clearly
specifies that the estate was used as
collateral so
can i set up some kind of payment plan
as the notice clearly states you have
until december 24th
to pay back the full amount owed
or the bank will have no other option
but to take full possession
of the estate on december 25th
christmas day
you heartless slime ball
it's not personal to you because it's
not misplacing your keys to your fancy
car or getting a stain on your nice suit
this means everything to me
[Music]
but you know i guess i'm just a customer
that takes everything too
personal
great job grant that's the type of ball
busting stick to your vigor that's gonna
get you straight to the top great job
my family business is all i have
damn
wait
what no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no
not this one all right we have to crush
her if we were going to make this
investment thing happen
all right we need this i need this
this always happens to me this always
happens to me the very moment
i'm ready for a relationship and i have
to chop her head off
it's like the mayans
yeah
look why don't you ask out that girl
that found your book she seemed nice
dude look word of warning if you're
gonna stick around for a while
don't upset the boss man
what's that
it's her necklace
she must have dropped it while she was
chewing me out
remember
don't upset the boss man
somebody can't do this this is like what
corporate sabotage or exhibition or
something
it's embarrassing that you work in a
library
how long will it take you to pay this
buddy oh you know i don't know 10 years
10 years what are they giving you till
till christmas till christmas
ah those syntax bankers
so i mean what are we going to do we
can't squeeze blood from a turnip turnip
maps relax this is merely a lemon and
we're going to make some lemonade oh no
no no i'm going to do way better than
that i am going to go to school for four
years i'm going to get a degree in
business i'm going to open a lemonade
stand i'm gonna hire a bunch of
employees to run that lemonade stand
probably an employee named paul who will
embezzle a bunch of money and i'm gonna
have to sue him but you know what i'll
get a settlement and then i'll buy all
the lemonade i want
stupid pull
brook your turn
i can think of a hundred different ways
to make money but not
nearly the amount that i need
i'm just literally drawing a blank
you'll come up with something
i just i feel like the big bad world
finally found me and is trying to take
everything i have
you know
tonight
i promise you
all those big heavy feelings that are
weighing you down
will be magically
whisked away
in a night of
romantic enchantment
hi welcome just two tonight the most
charming and hypnotic nook you have
available
please
follow me
[Music]
you
have been
so good to me
so fine
and so gentle
i
came around
and now i see
your face
so sentimentally
at first i thought
nothing of it all
[Music]
it's seen
just a passing fade
[Music]
i
hope
i don't wake you
can't sleep
i may need some advice from a stranger
well hello
you're not the only one who gets to stay
up past your bedtime
perhaps we can help each other you go
first
so
there's someone i've come to
despise
the very people that should be looking
out for me
may actually be trying to take advantage
of my ignorance
what should i do
if my suspicion is correct
anytime i'm confronted with a potential
enemy
i can keep it together carefully
befriend them
and learn their weakness
yes
your intuition is amazing
thank you for your empowering words of
wisdom
so
i've told you my struggles
how about you
what's a personal thing you've been
battling
well that's a painful task to ask for a
guy
huh well
besides an endless desire for sugar
cookies i would have to say
i struggle with
loneliness
just me and my son two bachelors
no females to argue with
oh
a son
the plot thickens
yeah
he's what keeps me going these days i
grew up with just my mom and sister and
we didn't have much
but she would remind me that we're rich
because we have each other
i know that sounds lame but i mean it
meant a lot to me when i was a kid you
know
sounds a lot like my dad
she taught me to never stop fighting for
the things i care about
so uh when it comes to family
i don't quit
that's
exactly where i'm at
i need to fight for the things i love
thanks rudy
for bearing your soul
good night sparks
[Music]
um jason let me call you back
uh did i miss an appointment
the wheel has come full circle and i am
here
men as sometimes think they're masters
of their fates the fault is not in the
stars but in ourselves julius caesar uh
what are you doing here
i
am saving shakespeare i'm pretty sure
he's already dead 3521.18
great
savings from under the mattress i take
it if you think for one second i'm just
going to roll over and let you take
everything from me including my house
you have another thing coming i am many
and we are saving shakespeare
it's all so good your passion
is electric but it's gonna take more
shoe boxes to save your precious little
ben breakfast the man robbed that smiles
steals something from the thief othello
i knew that one i know othello
i know all the othellos
[Music]
all right so
here's the plan
we're gonna need a lot more of these and
we're gonna put them all over the city
okay i mean every cafe every uh
restaurant even here at the library
because no amount of money is too small
okay
what do you think
save shakespeare chateau uh-huh
i think
probably use a little bit more theatrics
theatrics guys this is my sister katie
what's up
and you know lizzy yeah no she's bright
we need more theatrics if i prick my
finger
do i not bleed
if someone tickles me
do i not laugh
and or scream yes but if somebody steals
your bed and breakfast do you not
revenge
once more unto the breach dear friends
once more
save the chateau
[Music]
hello rudy it sparks again i wanted to
thank you
i took some of your advice about
fighting for the things i love and i
realized it was time to rescue my family
and our heritage
and i have to say
it feels good to finally start winning
[Music]
hey guys we made the paper let me see
that
saving shakespeare for christmas
let's have a look
[Music]
a historic landmark that has been open
to the public for decades losing this
beloved gem would be like losing a piece
of the city's very soul that's very
theatrical
the evil antagonist is once again the
big bad ambassador bank who sails in
accommodates poor small business victims
i'm sure you've
seen this
uh yes sir
i can have the newspaper retract the
article no no no
you look like a
bunch of pretentious idiots i want you
to do something
something unexpected
i want to help the bed and breakfast
help them by multiplying the money that
they're getting from these donations by
a hedge fund that we privately manage
really are you sure about that
i mean what if they make the payoff then
we lose the deal with bobusca don't
worry about babushka
i i need your help though
sure
can you bring in this mrs phipps
and get her to sign with us
yeah yeah yeah i mean i can i can try
i'm counting on you son
bring her in
[Music]
hi
welcome um are you at the donovan party
i'm actually here to see brooke is she
around
um she just stepped out she should be
back any minute
lots of guests out of out of groceries
yeah right
i'm katie hey i'm i'm grant a friend
i gotta tell you this place is really
beautiful yeah i um i i grew up here
really
i thought brooke was an only child
oh no there's there are three of us
three uh me brooke and our little sister
lizzy um katie we need more drinks in
the parlor okay so let me guess you're
the cute younger sister that runs this
place you know
[Music]
she's spirited that's a word for it
katie i'm back i need some help please
you know what
i'll take this one
she's all yours great to meet you you
too
uh what are you doing i wanted to see
how things were going well let me help
you out oh no you know actually i don't
i don't actually need your help
are you always as charming you know you
might be the exception but um i actually
have real guests to attend to so
if you don't mind
i'll just see you later
[Music]
so how about something to drink
what would you like oh water if you have
it
[Music]
you're gonna have wine
okay
so i'm curious
what was it like growing up in a
historic mansion
holidays here were the best
there is something magical about this
place at christmas
it literally takes your breath away
you might be onto something
i haven't had this much fun in years
this place is so romantic oh thank you
there you go well thanks
[Music]
yeah
you got it
nice moves
thanks
so tell me this
why do you call it the shakespeare
chateau
you see that carving right there my
granddad took it over and made a bed and
breakfast he used to read shakespearean
plays to all the guests and he would
stand right there by the fireplace
actually
so we called it the shakespeare chat
you really do love this place don't you
i know it's just a house
but
[Music]
it feels like more than that
you just gave me a compliment didn't you
oh okay
like just
put the glass down turn it down just
tone it down relax
[Music]
sweet company
why did you come by anyway
well there's uh something i wanted to
talk to you about
i might be able to help you make your
money back a little bit faster
just uh swing by the bank tomorrow and
i can show you
okay
but
i have to know why
why are you being so nice to me
you want me to stop
[Applause]
well uh thank you yes thanks very much
it was a pleasure
i'll see you tomorrow i will see you
tomorrow
tomorrow tomorrow
[Music]
me
mr ogden
miss phipps is here to see you oh yeah
uh
send her in
hi brooke hi grant please come in have a
seat
oh brook i've just got to say how
gorgeous your house is it's beautiful
well
thank you i'm i'm actually really happy
you got to see it um a photo doesn't
really you know
capture the beauty of a
thing
so am i supposed to sign some papers
yeah uh your paperwork that is why
you're here my boss mr valorsky he's
getting the paperwork together right now
that's that's being done okay yeah
you know what
we should go on a tour
let me show you around
pretty great isn't it um
hand-painted murals
stained glass windows
and we still have the original vaults
wow
there's actually two sets of faults this
is the lower
fault
this is where people store their most
treasured things
hmm
guess there's two sides to everything
here huh
grant there you are
miss phipps i ask him hello and you are
frank polorski president and chairman of
the board of ambassador bank oh
um brooke mr volorski was so moved by
your story now that it's in all the
newspapers you decided to step in and
help out
what do you know about hedge funds
uh
nothing
see we heard about your unfortunate
balloon note and we want to keep you the
customer well what do you need for me
well you could take the money you raised
from the fundraiser uh put it into the
account triple your money cash out pay
the balloon note
it's that simple
i'm not really good with these kind of
things i just
grant honestly do you think this is the
right thing to do
i
think this might just work yeah
okay
let's do it okay so an initial of these
two places
okay these next pages are just a bunch
of contract stuff yadda yadda the
initial right there
great
okay
congratulations miss phipps you've made
the right choice
have a nice day thank you
[Music]
yeah
wow
um that was a rush
thank you again thank you i um very
welcome
i will um
i will be back later to deposit that
money perfect i'll see you then okay all
right i'll see you
bye
okay
[Music]
all my lonely
days are over
and my nights
are filled with joy
all those lonely days have gone away in
my heart's like a little toy
with my lone
days behind me
i can
[Music]
say goodbye
hey there sparks
you're officially now my personal
therapist
since we've started texting that
loneliness i used to have well
it's faded away i really feel like i'm
connecting to the people around me
even opening up more
which is uh a big deal for me
how about you
that's crazy
i've been feeling the same lately if you
don't mind
may i hold on to that book a little
longer i really don't want to jinx
what's been happening
[Music]
and she finally had the one her heart
loved and she came down the path from
the mountain of love
she came down the path
someone's happy
no just
reading a book about love
no
the lady doth protest too much often the
pure innocence of silence persuades
where words fail
quote
a winter's tale
you just told on yourself and i'm pretty
sure sean has nothing to do with it
[Music]
hello sparks it's rudy again
listen how about this i buy you a
month's worth of coffee at the brioche
and if it's not too much to ask
will you still be my pen pal
i need a female to argue with
uh
sure
i love a good argument
whatever chris's magic we've started
baking let's not stop
life is tasting a bit sweeter
[Music]
hello sparks just curious
what happened to that person you had
come to despise
did you ever learn their weakness
hey there rudy
actually
yeah
i think i did
[Music]
good night
sparks
[Music]
i'm thinking
something sugary and tasty i'm getting
the usual dark thick and lonely
we have a special on peppermint mocha
the spirit of the holidays
that sounds good i will have one of
those please why not you had me at
peppermint mocha
that'll be 3.75 a piece please
i can't wait to try this
your crime's declined ma'am
i'm sorry it's it's new can you try it
one more time
it's still the same man
i don't understand i mean i
it's i got this one
i got this one
what do you mean there's less than 200
in my account i mean i i just deposited
thousands of dollars literally two days
ago i'm sorry ma'am but your account's
been frozen until the funds have been
deposited this is insane
what's going on
oh brook hey there
there's no money in my account it's it's
not there it's just gone and i wait
what are you talking about i just tried
to use my bank card and it got declined
they said there's not efficient funds in
the account and i just need to know
where my money is all right let me pull
up your account i'm sure it's an error
on our end no i'm sorry i i really don't
mean to overreact i just i get it brooke
i get it don't get between a woman and
her money
all right what do we got here
hmm
that's strange what
there are no funds
i don't understand this
i'm sorry brocada
i don't know how this
you planned this
hey bro wait wait we can figure this out
brooke
come on brooke brooke wait i'm sorry we
can figure this out
i don't want to see you
i don't want to talk to you i want
nothing to do with you i'm sure there's
something we can do
i trusted you
and now
i have nothing
we need to talk now
ah there he is the hammer hitting work
counts you knew this was gonna happen
mission accomplished great job grant do
you feel anything i mean do you have any
remorse for stealing people's money i
get it
you're personally attached
oh that's a big no-no
you know grant
i like you
saw what was happening
decided to put a leash on you
she doesn't deserve this
you know you'll forget in time we all
had to
oh and um
a word of advice
don't let this
little thing
ruin what you've been building here
[Music]
hello again
it's
sparked
i'm sorry if this sounds weird but
my life has just
fallen apart
it's
been a crazy few days so
i'm just gonna come out and say it i
really need to meet you
i need to see you face to face to know
that
you're real
will you meet me
[Music]
hello there
everything you just described is exactly
what i've been going through
finally meeting you would mean a lot to
me
can it be soon
i thought you'd never ask
how about
now
[Music]
you read my mind the brioche closes in
two hours
meet in 30.
i will be there
you
and me
dancing
slow
motion you
and me
here in these arms
[Music]
you
and me
[Music]
is
oh
[Music]
is
i just
i can't believe it we're
we're really gonna lose a chateau
i'm glad we were able to meet tonight
i have something that i've been wanting
to
tell you
wow
nervous
just
take your time
you and i have really
shared some special moments i'd say
and i just think that i am
falling in love
with this extraordinary girl from
rehearsal
i'm crazy in love with her she's crazy
in love with me and we're both crazy in
love
so you and i need to break up
what
i'm breaking up with you brooke
you are so great
for some other guy you know
well
that's just great
i can't believe this
that's me a failure i i need a big sign
that says brook fitz failure at
everything her life her family her
friends and
oh
wow
i should have seen it earlier
you were made for the theater my vixen
call this number
i'll put a big word in for you
okay
[Music]
hey brock we made some cookies
how was your date
[Music]
i lost the chateau
wait you
what do you mean
bro
[Music]
i take it things didn't go so well
you know how some people have that magic
touch
makes everything turn to gold
mine break stuff
[Music]
then you lean on the others around you
let their strength
keep your standing
that's why we have love
it's what
anything substantial is built on love
our family
is built upon the foundation
[Music]
i'll always be proud of your sparks
always
i love you dad
[Music]
dad what is this place that is your
librarian's house librarians must be
rich
want to go outside yeah let's do it
[Music]
all right we need a refill on the chips
hi
it's me
you have no right to be here so uh
please leave
i've been a schlub but you haven't let
me apologize you know there's really
nothing else to say
but there is there is something to say
who are all these people anyways
every year we invite the homeless so
they can have a warm meal that's
incredible
i wish i was more like that see that's
why i need you in my life brooke to help
me be a better man
to make you feel better
that's exactly what a self-centered
person would say please do this so my
pain can stop while i waltz all over
your heart
see that's where you're wrong if you
would just stop listen and not jump to
conclusions you might realize that
people actually care and i care about
you don't give me that garbage i can
read you like a book
oh really
okay then why am i standing in the
middle of your house eating your food oh
because i know there's something between
us and you know too there is nothing
between us
and there never will be you tried to
play your little charm game but it was
all a lie and i
i could never be with a man like you i
don't believe that
and i know you don't believe that
so you can honestly say you never felt
anything
you want honesty grant
i trusted you you tricked me and now i'm
losing everything okay i never tricked
you i was completely honest with you
from the beginning all right and oh do
you remember i even tried helping you oh
so this is all their fault you're insane
you can't just waltz into someone's life
destroy their heart and then expect them
to ever trust you again
so you were falling for me
this is just great just great oh i'm the
luckiest man in the world the woman i
love
was falling for me and now she hates my
guts oh
man
you could never love anyone but yourself
you're the most greedy selfish man i
have ever met in my life in fact it is
no wonder you're a single father you
probably constantly woman into sleeping
with you and then when she figured you
out she left you
she was my wife
brooke
she died of cancer
and every time i look at my little boy
i see her face
[Music]
dad there's a boss that plays music
without the internet
can we spend the night
no
not tonight
hey time to go bud go grab your code
okay
i uh
i got you something
[Music]
merry christmas
hey
think of it as a new adventure
[Music]
there's a whole wide world out there
okay
[Music]
hey sports come on baby girl
dance with us give me just one second i
got cookies in the oven about to burn i
will be right back i promise but it's
tradition
[Music]
promise me you won't let this place run
your life
whenever it comes to stumbling block
don't hesitate let it go
this place is not
our family
we
are our family
promise me
i promise
[Music]
i know he missed
her i think he was just
waiting
for the moment that he would see her
again
and the life after this
[Music]
dad
sparks is that you
[Music]
do you remember
the last time we danced
the good christmas eve
the gifts the lights
music
i love you dad
i love you two sparks
the whole setting was perfect
all three of my
lovely girls were there
[Music]
dad i'm sorry
i
i tried i really tried to save
don't cry
he's listening
he hears your
your pain
every feeling your heart makes
he feels it all
he's been there the whole time
they feel so alone
why didn't you have to go
i wasn't ready i i wasn't ready for you
to leave me oh darling
people will always go
and god will never leave you an orphan
sweetheart
he'll always be there for you
he's been carrying you this whole time
brooke
you're right
hey
[Music]
i know it's uh
it's hard
he told me to look out for you
it's almost like he knew right
yeah
[Music]
it's time
you have to let him go
you'll be all right
queen of your sparks
thanks
[Music]
um
there's still one gift
it's not for me it's
it's from grant
[Music]
he really cares for you brooke
hey there sparks i haven't heard from
you in a while
i've been thinking who better to pour
out my soul
than to the girl i've never met
secretly
i've drank more coffee in the last three
weeks than i have my whole life
mentally preparing myself for that cup
of coffee
i was gonna share with you
[Music]
when we first started messaging
i really thought this was it
this was the reason i found myself in
this little town
it was to meet you
whoever you were
[Music]
that maybe destiny was real
that maybe if if i put myself out there
we would find each other
but i want you to know that whether
you're real or not
i believe in what could have been
the thought that one day we would meet
and realize we had just been looking for
each other
our whole lives we were just trying to
find
us
regretfully i've decided to leave town
and i probably won't be back
i want to at least give you the book
that started our wonderful conversations
since i don't know who you are or where
to find you i'll leave it at the same
place you found it
the brioche
maybe it will remind you of brighter
days
perhaps in another life we may have made
a great couple
i care for you
whoever you are
no
no stupid phone
i'm here i'm here
the cafe
[Music]
so
ah
[Music]
you
and me
[Music]
[Applause]
dad someone's here
it's you
[Music]
here
are you sparks
[Music]
your sparks
i didn't think you were gonna show here
[Music]
why why did you come back
because i owe you coffee actually i owe
you a few coffees i was going to leave
these here before we left
and how many
coffees that take you to acquire these
a lot
for the past month
i
waited
for you to text me
hoping for you to text me
not knowing it was you
you hurt me grant
so bad and i
i
hate you for that
but
it took me losing everything to realize
that
i was stuck
i was stuck in that house and i
[Music]
i am not that house
i want to hate you
[Music]
but i can't
i've got you sparks
can we give you a ride home
yeah
sure
all right
[Music]
suddenly
she passes right in from me
[Music]
suddenly
feels like i'm gonna fall
well
it's been a few months since we lost the
house to mr bill buska
the bigwig investor from ambassador bank
and yes
it was on christmas day i mean talk
about getting the holiday blues that was
the icing on the cake excuse me who's
telling the story oh sorry babe you are
go ahead
so
about two weeks after grant and i fell
in love
and i was forced out of the chateau
the irs came visiting ambassador bank
and found some
interesting paperwork that didn't quite
hold up well in court
i mean i may have known someone who knew
someone that may have blown the whistle
so
hakuna matata i mean that's shakespeare
right
no
that's the lion king
the bank's properties were put up for
auction i mean pennies on the dollar
including the shakespeare chateau so
we
we bought it back i'm cutting in i can't
help it we bought that baby back and for
cheaper than what your loan was
it was a joint loan since your credit
was shot thanks to you
you're welcome so are you gonna tell
them about the best part he can't leave
out the best part babe
and
we ended up getting married there
that was my idea great idea huh
nope pretty sure i came up with that one
and now we both run the bed and
breakfast together
with my sisters of course
[Music]
it can't take away
the hope that you feel
[Music]
across empty miles
you know that it's real
it's out there waiting
[Music]
soon to be revealed
somewhere
[Music]
waiting for you